<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Fight for the Future</title>
    <description>Fight for the Future is dedicated to protecting and expanding the Internet's transformative power in our lives by creating civic campaigns that are engaging for millions of people.</description>
    <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org</link>
    <atom:link href="https://www.fightforthefuture.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Over 500 small businesses sign open letter to FCC and Congress urging them to preserve Title II net neutrality protections</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;507&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1046&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/9dfa83b65e0f533dd63b8599d49a7b35/tumblr_inline_ovk21b1TrY1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;507&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1046&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, August 31, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Businesses from across the US tell lawmakers how losing net neutrality would threaten their ability to reach customers and grow their businesses online&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;August 31, 2017 – Late yesterday, a group of over 500 small businesses and trade associations from across the country signed &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.keepthewebopenforbusiness.com/FCC_17-108_smallbusiness-ASBC-filing-170830.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;an open letter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; raising concerns over the Federal Communications Commission’s (FCC) plan to repeal net neutrality. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.keepthewebopenforbusiness.com/FCC_17-108_smallbusiness-ASBC-filing-170830.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;letter&lt;/a&gt;, filed with the FCC by the American Sustainable Business Council, warns that “weakening or rolling back the 2015 protections would be disastrous for the country’s business community” who for decades have relied on open access to the open Internet to do business.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The signatories–ranging from dentist offices to sporting goods stores–highlight how the FCC’s proposed changes would put smaller business at a disadvantage with larger companies. Without strong protections Internet service providers (ISPs) would be permitted to block websites, slow traffic, or charge new access fees. The businesses warn policymakers that, “While big companies might be able to afford a pay-to-play prioritized ‘fast lane’ to users, small and medium sized enterprises like ours cannot.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Small and medium sized businesses are encouraged to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.keepthewebopenforbusiness.com/#letter&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sign on&lt;/a&gt;, as names are being added on rolling basis at &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.keepthewebopenforbusiness.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;KeepTheWebOpenForBusiness.com&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“These businesses represent their founders’ dreams for a better life and a better world—and they’re how many families put food on the table and pay their bills each month,” &lt;b&gt;said Fight for the Future co-founder Holmes Wilson,&lt;/b&gt; “The FCC’s plan to end net neutrality puts businesses like these—and the livelihoods of the millions of people that depend on them—in grave danger.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The letter was filed on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2017/08/30/today-is-your-last-chance-to-comment-on-the-proposal-to-kill-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;final day&lt;/a&gt; of the FCC’s controversial net neutrality consultation, which sparked millions of comments, emails, and phone calls in support of Title II following the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dailydot.com/layer8/net-neutrality-day-of-action-fcc-comments/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;July 12th day of action&lt;/a&gt;. Earlier this week digital rights group Fight for the Future released a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.broadcastingcable.com/news/washington/more-net-neutrality-billboards-go/168195&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;second wave&lt;/a&gt; of billboards targeting members of Congress who support the FCC’s repeal, building on an &lt;a href=&quot;https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2017/08/pro-net-neutrality-billboards-shame-lawmakers-who-want-to-repeal-rules/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;initial round&lt;/a&gt; of six billboards from earlier this month. The ads are currently running in nine different states while lawmakers are back in their home districts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future is best known for their role in the massive online protests against SOPA, the Stop Online Piracy Act, and continues to organize many of the largest protests in the history of the Internet. They recently organized the high profile Rock Against the TPP tour, as well as historic July 12th Internet-wide day of action to save net neutrality. Learn more at FightFortheFuture.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 11:08:06 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-31-over-500-small-businesses-sign-open-letter-to-fcc/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-31-over-500-small-businesses-sign-open-letter-to-fcc/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cable industry’s own study shows their plan to kill net neutrality is as unpopular as ever</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, August 30, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;While FCC’s refusal to address cybersecurity issues and fake comments creates intentional confusion around data, unique comments are overwhelmingly in favor of Title II net neutrality— by more than 73 to 1&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, the telecom industry is touting &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.emprata.com/reports/fcc-restoring-internet-freedom-docket/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;a study&lt;/a&gt; funded by cable lobby group Broadband for America regarding the millions of comments submitted to the FCC’s public docket surrounding the agency’s plan to gut Title II net neutrality rules that prevent companies like AT&amp;amp;T and Verizon from charging extra fees, throttling apps and services, and censoring online content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The most telling statistic in the report is that the unique comments in the docket &amp;ndash; the ones that people took the extra time to write themselves &amp;ndash; are overwhelmingly in favor of Title II net neutrality protections, by more than 73 to 1. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;152&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;750&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/1a358f0e4292d6d7cc8ecb151144bf5b/tumblr_inline_ovi9hz2vks1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;152&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;750&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;So the telecom industry’s &lt;b&gt;own study&lt;/b&gt; essentially shows what nearly &lt;a href=&quot;http://thehill.com/policy/technology/341850-poll-gop-voters-support-net-neutrality-rules-oppose-att-time-warner-merger&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;all&lt;/a&gt; other &lt;a href=&quot;http://thehill.com/policy/technology/339137-poll-60-percent-of-voters-support-fccs-net-neutrality-rules&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;polling&lt;/a&gt; on this issue &lt;a href=&quot;https://morningconsult.com/2017/06/21/poll-shows-broad-bipartisan-support-net-neutrality-rules/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;has shown&lt;/a&gt;: that they are getting trounced when it comes to public opinion, and people from across the political spectrum overwhelmingly agree that they don’t want their ISPs to have control over what they can see and do on the Internet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The report also highlights that the data in the FCC docket is a mess. Fight for the Future has been working with a group of tech volunteers to analyze this data as well, and will be releasing our findings soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much of the reporting on this study draws a false equivalence between real comments from real people gathered through grassroots activism campaigns with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-13-update-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;massive&lt;/a&gt; public participation &amp;ndash; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.comcastroturf.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;completely fraudulent comments&lt;/a&gt; that use names and addresses from breached databases, or completely fake information. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sadly, this confusion appears to be by design. Under Ajit Pai’s leadership, the FCC has repeatedly refused to address serious cybersecurity and transparency issues surrounding their public comment process, from the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-07-breaking-former-fcc-security-employee-destroys/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;now debunked&lt;/a&gt; claims of DDoS attacks to the confirmed fraudulent comments that the agency won’t remove from its docket. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The agency is sabotaging the legitimacy of its own proceeding in a cynical attempt to spread confusion about something that is actually as clear as day: the majority of the voices calling for the end of net neutrality protections are those bought and paid for by the industry that stands to gain unprecedented control of our online experience if they succeed in rigging the game and gutting these consumer protections at the FCC or through bad legislation billed as a “compromise.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 11:44:41 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-30-cable-industrys-own-study-shows-their-plan-to/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-30-cable-industrys-own-study-shows-their-plan-to/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Net neutrality advocates release more crowdfunded billboards exposing key lawmakers who are supporting the FCC’s net neutrality repeal</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;3456&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;4608&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/bc4946c40d136e17ab4533eed55b1db0/tumblr_inline_ovgfv2Pgo71ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;3456&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;4608&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, August 29, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, press@fightforthefuture.org, 978-852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;New billboards in three states single out members of Congress who support the FCC’s plan to gut rules stopping ISPs from charging new fees, slowing traffic, or blocking websites&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today digital rights organization Fight for the Future unveiled 3 more crowdfunded billboards targeting Representatives &lt;b&gt;Cathy McMorris Rodgers&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt; Bob Latta,&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;Greg Walden&lt;/b&gt;, members of Congress who have publicly supported the FCC’s efforts to gut net neutrality protections that keep the web free from censorship, throttling, and extra fees. The three new billboards are the latest in an ongoing campaign focused on lawmakers who oppose Internet freedom. Earlier this month the group launched an initial&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2017/08/pro-net-neutrality-billboards-shame-lawmakers-who-want-to-repeal-rules/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;round of net neutrality&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;billboards&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; targeting six different lawmakers in states across the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The move comes just hours before the FCC’s&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2017/8/11/16135708/fcc-net-neutrality-comment-period-extended-two-weeks&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;final deadline for public input&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;on their controversial plan to repeal net neutrality. With lawmakers still in their home districts, the billboards -&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://donate.fightforthefuture.org/campaigns/nnbillboards/#page-1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;paid for&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;by hundreds of small donations - appear in three different states.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS of the 3 new billboards here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/UHfXJ&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/a/UHfXJ&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the massive July 12th day of action, millions have contacted their representatives – who have oversight over the FCC – to ensure these key protections are not changed or removed. The billboards send a strong message to any Members of Congress contemplating support for the FCC’s plan to repeal net neutrality, which is currently being tracked through a &lt;b&gt;“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/#scoreboard&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;congressional scorecard&lt;/a&gt;” &lt;/b&gt;on BattleForTheNet.com. So far very few lawmakers have been willing to publicly support Ajit Pai’s plan, likely in light of polling that shows voters &amp;ndash; including Republicans &amp;ndash; overwhelmingly oppose it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;411&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;643&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/ad389d5c048d96ca1756cd5c7ed6f993/tumblr_inline_ovgfv7AHwI1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;411&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;643&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The billboards encourage constituents to contact their elected representatives; for example, Committee on Energy and Commerce Chairman Rep. Greg Walden’s (R-OR) billboard in Medford, Oregon asks, “Want slower, more expensive Internet? Rep. Walden supports CenturyLink’s plan to destroy net neutrality. Ask him why: (541) 776-4646.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The outdoor ads feature some of the few members of Congress who came out with early support for FCC’s plan to repeal net neutrality rules, including:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Spokane, WA &lt;/b&gt;– Rep. Cathy McMorris Rodgers (N. Monroe Street at W. Broadway Ave)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Findlay, OH &lt;/b&gt;– Rep. Bob Latta (corner of E Main Cross St and East St.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Medford, OR&lt;/b&gt; – Rep. Greg Walden (N. Pacific Hwy at Elm Ave)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It doesn’t matter which party you’re in, or how charming you are on TV &amp;ndash; if you attack net neutrality and Internet freedom we will make sure everyone knows that you’re corrupt to the core” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future (pronouns: she/hers), &lt;/b&gt;“every member of Congress should take note: supporting the FCC’s plan to allow censorship, throttling, and price gouging may get you a few extra campaign donations from big telecom companies, but it will infuriate your constituents, and will come with a serious political cost.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The billboards highlight the increasing scrutiny on Congress - who have important oversight authority over the FCC. With no viable legislation on the table, net neutrality supporters remain opposed to any attempt at legislation that would undermine the strong rules at the FCC, which were fought for by millions of Americans, and are calling on lawmakers to publicly oppose Ajit Pai’s plan, and require the FCC to act with transparency and address &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/163913891863/breaking-former-fcc-security-employee-destroys&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;serious irregularities&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in its rulemaking process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future was also one of the leading organizations behind the historic Internet-Wide Day of Action for Net Neutrality on July 12,&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.fightforthefuture.org%2Fnews%2F2017-07-13-update-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality%2F&amp;amp;t=YmFhMmU0MGQ2YWEzMTJmMDcxYzRlYjJjMGRmNjE0YzgxODhmOTcwNCx2cnltU0FjZQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F163913891863%2Fbreaking-former-fcc-security-employee-destroys&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;which drove&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; a record breaking 2 million+ comments to the FCC and Congress in a single day. Learn more at &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Ffightforthefuture.org&amp;amp;t=NDc0NWJkZWMwYTkyY2UyZDNmN2FhOTU0MjI3NGUzYzk0NDMxZjNlNix2cnltU0FjZQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F163913891863%2Fbreaking-former-fcc-security-employee-destroys&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;554&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;730&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/ba97e7010820a4d2ac5f8fa361f54708/tumblr_inline_ovgfvjOMkb1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;554&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;730&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 12:16:59 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-29-net-neutrality-advocates-release-more-crowdfunded/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-29-net-neutrality-advocates-release-more-crowdfunded/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Net neutrality activists launch crowdfunded billboards targeting key members of Congress during August recess</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;728&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;400&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/1bd85ccb097a41ccbe5990b397f2781e/tumblr_inline_ouq674OTlq1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;728&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;400&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, August 15, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Tiffiniy Cheng, 413-367-6255, press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Billboards in six states single out lawmakers who support the FCC’s plan to gut key safeguards preventing ISPs from charging new fees, slowing traffic, or blocking websites&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today digital rights organization Fight for the Future unleashed a series of crowdfunded billboards targeting lawmakers who support FCC Chairman Ajit Pai’s efforts to repeal the country’s net neutrality rules. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With members of Congress back in their home districts, the billboards -&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://donate.fightforthefuture.org/campaigns/nnbillboards/#page-1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;paid for&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;by hundreds of small donations - appear in six different states just weeks before the FCC’s final deadline for public input on their proposal to gut net neutrality rules that prevent companies like Comcast, Verizon, and AT&amp;amp;T from charging extra fees, throttling, or blocking websites, apps, and online services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS of some of the billboards here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/lhEko&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/a/lhEko&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the massive July 12th day of action, millions have contacted their representatives – who have oversight over the FCC – to ensure these key protections are not changed or removed. The billboards send a strong message to any Members of Congress contemplating support for the FCC’s plan to repeal net neutrality, which is currently being tracked through a &lt;b&gt;“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/#scoreboard&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;congressional scorecard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;” on BattleForTheNet.com. So far very few lawmakers have been willing to publicly support Ajit Pai’s plan, likely in light of polling that shows voters &amp;ndash; including Republicans &amp;ndash; overwhelmingly oppose it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;3073&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1417&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/43709916731ba6fa49023c4087876433/tumblr_inline_ouq6amcwc61ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3073&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1417&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The billboards encourage constituents to contact their elected representatives; for example, Speaker Paul Ryan’s billboard in Janesville, WI asks, “Want slower, more expensive Internet? Rep. Paul Ryan supports Charter’s plan to destroy net neutrality. Ask him why: (608) 752-4050.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The outdoor ads feature some of the few members of Congress who came out with early support for FCC’s plan to repeal net neutrality rules, including:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clarksville, TN – Rep. Marsha Blackburn (Sources: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2017/05/31/blackburn-fccs-rollback-net-neutrality-rules-a-positive-step/356558001/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;USA Today&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://energycommerce.house.gov/news-center/press-releases/bicameral-leaders-comment-pai-s-internet-regulations-announcement&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Energy and Commerce Committee media release&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2017/01/enemy-of-net-neutrality-and-muni-broadband-will-chair-house-telecom-panel/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ars Technica&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dalton, GA – Rep. Tom Graves (Sources: &lt;a href=&quot;https://act.represent.us/sign/Net_neutrality_contributions/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Represent.us&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://tomgraves.house.gov/newsroom/documentsingle.aspx?DocumentID=398756&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;media release&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/RepTomGraves/status/857349425538248704&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bakersfield, CA – Rep. Kevin McCarthy (Sources: &lt;a href=&quot;http://thehill.com/policy/technology/341867-house-republican-leadership-cautions-tech-on-net-neutrality-report&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Hill&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.axios.com/republicans-nudge-big-tech-over-net-neutrality-activism-2458262562.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Axios&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2014/06/20/new-house-majority-leader-opposes-net-neutrality-just-like-his-predecessor/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;TechCrunch&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Janesville, WI– Rep. Paul Ryan (Sources: &lt;a href=&quot;http://thehill.com/policy/technology/330754-ryan-cheers-fcc-chiefs-plans-to-roll-back-net-neutrality&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Hill&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://thehill.com/policy/technology/341867-house-republican-leadership-cautions-tech-on-net-neutrality-report&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Hill&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rapid City, SD – Sen. John Thune (Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://energycommerce.house.gov/news-center/press-releases/bicameral-leaders-comment-pai-s-internet-regulations-announcement&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Energy and Commerce Committee media release&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Jackson, MS – Sen. Roger Wicker (Sources: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.incompas.org/files/IMGEInsights-Presentations-KeyFindings-1c.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;INCOMPAS poll&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.mozilla.org/blog/2017/06/06/new-mozilla-poll-americans-political-parties-overwhelmingly-support-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mozilla poll&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://energycommerce.house.gov/news-center/press-releases/bicameral-leaders-comment-pai-s-internet-regulations-announcement&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;media release&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Politicians need to learn that they can’t attack free speech on the Internet and expect to get away with it,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future (pronouns: she/hers), &lt;/b&gt;“Voters from across the political spectrum all agree that they don’t want companies like Comcast and Verizon dictating what they can see and do online. No one is fooled by corrupt lawmakers’ attempts to push for bad legislation while they strip Internet users of protections at the FCC. Hundreds of people donated to make these billboards possible. When you come for the Internet, the Internet comes for you.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;2851&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1467&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/ce131a0c2be5f848ec6054900d0cc6c5/tumblr_inline_ouq6dcuGgv1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;2851&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1467&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The billboards highlight the increasing scrutiny on Congress - who have important oversight authority over the FCC. With no viable legislation on the table, net neutrality supporters remain opposed to any attempt at legislation that would undermine the strong rules at the FCC, which were fought for by millions of Americans, and are calling on lawmakers to publicly oppose Ajit Pai’s plan, and require the FCC to act with transparency and address &lt;a href=&quot;http://tumblr.fightforthefuture.org/post/163913891863/breaking-former-fcc-security-employee-destroys&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;serious &lt;b&gt;irregularities&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;in its rulemaking process. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future was also one of the leading organizations behind the historic Internet-Wide Day of Action for Net Neutrality on July 12, &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.fightforthefuture.org%2Fnews%2F2017-07-13-update-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality%2F&amp;amp;t=YmFhMmU0MGQ2YWEzMTJmMDcxYzRlYjJjMGRmNjE0YzgxODhmOTcwNCx2cnltU0FjZQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F163913891863%2Fbreaking-former-fcc-security-employee-destroys&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;which drove&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; a record breaking 2 million+ comments to the FCC and Congress in a single day. Learn more at&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Ffightforthefuture.org&amp;amp;t=NDc0NWJkZWMwYTkyY2UyZDNmN2FhOTU0MjI3NGUzYzk0NDMxZjNlNix2cnltU0FjZQ%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F163913891863%2Fbreaking-former-fcc-security-employee-destroys&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;571&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;856&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/eb00a4a7e8d8476ad087da9da007d450/tumblr_inline_ouq6e45MqU1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;571&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;856&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;SOURCES FOR BILLBOARDS:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Where do the featured lawmakers stand?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rep. Marsha Blackburn: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/2017/05/31/blackburn-fccs-rollback-net-neutrality-rules-a-positive-step/356558001/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;USA Today&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://energycommerce.house.gov/news-center/press-releases/bicameral-leaders-comment-pai-s-internet-regulations-announcement&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Energy and Commerce Committee press release&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2017/01/enemy-of-net-neutrality-and-muni-broadband-will-chair-house-telecom-panel/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ars Technica&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rep. Tom Graves: &lt;a href=&quot;https://act.represent.us/sign/Net_neutrality_contributions/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Represent.us&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://tomgraves.house.gov/newsroom/documentsingle.aspx?DocumentID=398756&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rep. Graves&amp;rsquo; press release&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/RepTomGraves/status/857349425538248704&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@RepTomGraves tweet&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rep. Kevin McCarthy: &lt;a href=&quot;http://thehill.com/policy/technology/341867-house-republican-leadership-cautions-tech-on-net-neutrality-report&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Hill&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.axios.com/republicans-nudge-big-tech-over-net-neutrality-activism-2458262562.html&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Axios&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2014/06/20/new-house-majority-leader-opposes-net-neutrality-just-like-his-predecessor/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;TechCrunch&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rep. Paul Ryan: &lt;a href=&quot;http://thehill.com/policy/technology/330754-ryan-cheers-fcc-chiefs-plans-to-roll-back-net-neutrality&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Hill&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;http://thehill.com/policy/technology/341867-house-republican-leadership-cautions-tech-on-net-neutrality-report&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Hill&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sen. John Thune: &lt;a href=&quot;https://energycommerce.house.gov/news-center/press-releases/bicameral-leaders-comment-pai-s-internet-regulations-announcement&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Energy and Commerce Committee press release&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sen. Roger Wicker: &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.incompas.org/files/IMGEInsights-Presentations-KeyFindings-1c.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;INCOMPAS poll&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.mozilla.org/blog/2017/06/06/new-mozilla-poll-americans-political-parties-overwhelmingly-support-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mozilla poll&lt;/a&gt;, or &lt;a href=&quot;https://energycommerce.house.gov/news-center/press-releases/bicameral-leaders-comment-pai-s-internet-regulations-announcement&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Energy and Commerce Committee press release&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;What is at stake if we lose strong net neutrality rules? &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;“Under the current net neutrality rules, broadband providers like Comcast and Charter, and wireless providers like AT&amp;amp;T and Verizon, can&amp;rsquo;t block or slow down your access to lawful content, nor can they create so-called &amp;ldquo;fast lanes&amp;rdquo; for content providers who are willing to pay extra.”&lt;/i&gt;  Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/story/why-net-neutrality-matters-even-in-the-age-of-oligopoly/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;WIRED&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;‘In dispute are a set of U.S. federal regulations saying that internet providers should not slow down, block or charge websites extra fees while treating other sites differently. The Federal Communications Commission is currently weighing how to repeal those so-called “net neutrality” rules, in a move that’s expected to benefit internet providers such as Verizon and AT&amp;amp;T.’&lt;/i&gt; Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/the-switch/wp/2017/07/11/your-favorite-websites-might-look-a-little-different-soon-heres-why/?utm_term=.c90e573ee862&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Washington Post&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2017 09:51:42 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-15-net-neutrality-activists-launch-crowdfunded/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-15-net-neutrality-activists-launch-crowdfunded/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>BREAKING: former FCC security employee destroys agency’s claims of DDoS attacks following John Oliver net neutrality segments</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;614&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;560&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/f1a5ba1c8a2fd74f00929b22c3c46896/tumblr_inline_oubvczLsoL1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;614&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;560&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, August 7, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;, 978-852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Bombshell story from Gizmodo underscores need for FCC to address serious issues with its public comment process before making any decision on net neutrality. 15,000+ people call on lawmakers to demand that FCC comply with transparency laws&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a &lt;a href=&quot;http://gizmodo.com/senior-us-official-claimed-the-fcc-got-hacked-after-sec-1797593781&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;bombshell story&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; from Gizmodo today, a former FCC security employee lays waste to the agency’s claims that a pair of &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-20-fcc-now-says-it-has-no-documentation-of-ddos/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DDoS attacks&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;took down the FCC comment website at the exact moments when large amounts of pro net neutrality comments would have been flooding into the docket following viral segments from comedian John Oliver in 2014 and 2017. The agency’s inability to maintain a functional way for the public to comment on its net neutrality proceedings has become an issue of concern for members of Congress overseeing the agency, and raises questions about how it can or should move forward with its rulemaking process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The security expert who spoke to Gizmodo reveals that the FCC security team concluded that there had not been a malicious attack after the John Oliver segment in 2014. But until-recent FCC CIO David Bray told reporters that anyway, despite the fact there was no evidence of it, and he did not even have access to the types of logs and information that could have led him to that conclusion. The source also leaked a photo of the FCC’s server room to Gizmodo, revealing a mess of wires that would make any competent IT professional cringe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When pressed, Bray admitted to being the source of news reports about the made up “hacking” attack, but he never reported the incident to the Department of Homeland Security, who require that government agencies notify them of such attacks. With the backing of the FCC press office, Bray fed reporters that exact same story when the agency’s comment system collapsed again this year, preventing large numbers of people from making their voices heard in the agency’s proceeding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, said:&lt;/b&gt; “These latest revelations are outrageous. A senior FCC official intentionally misled the public and invented cyber attacks to cover up the fact that the agency is failing at their responsibility to maintain a functioning system to receive feedback about an issue that affects every single person using the Internet. The FCC must address these serious issues with their comment process before moving forward, or it will be clear that this is a rogue agency that answers only to large telecom companies, and not to the American people.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The news comes after more than 15,000 people signed &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://actionnetwork.org/petitions/tell-congress-demand-that-the-fcc-comply-with-transparency-laws&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;a petition&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;calling on their lawmakers to instruct the FCC to comply with transparency laws as the agency moves ahead with its unpopular plan to gut net neutrality protections that prevent ISPs from charging extra fees, throttling, or blocking content online. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The agency is currently facing multiple lawsuits for refusing to release information related to the now-debunked DDoS claims, Chairman Ajit Pai’s discussions with telecom companies,  large amounts of &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-06-12-more-than-15000-people-call-on-the-fcc-to-remove/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;fake comments&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;using real people’s names and addresses without their permission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Members of Congress need to understand that this is not an issue they can ignore or hide from,” &lt;b&gt;Greer added,&lt;/b&gt; “Voters from across the political spectrum overwhelmingly support the current net neutrality rules, and want their Senators and Representatives to do their job and speak out to ensure that the FCC is listening to the will of the public, not just to lobbyists from giant telecom companies. Lawmakers from both sides of the aisle need to exercise their oversight and demand that the FCC act transparently during this proceeding.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future has been working to inform the public about the serious issues surrounding the FCC’s comment process. The group organized &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-05-25-letter-to-the-fcc-from-people-whose-names-and/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;a letter&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;from dozens of people whose names and addresses were used to submit anti net neutrality comments without their permission, as well as several petitions garnering tens of thousands of signatures calling on the agency to come clean about the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-20-fcc-now-says-it-has-no-documentation-of-ddos/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;alleged DDoS&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt; &lt;/b&gt;attack that prevented concerned citizens from submitting comments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future was also one of the leading organizations behind the historic Internet-Wide Day of Action for Net Neutrality on July 12, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-13-update-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;which drove&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; a record breaking 2 million+ comments to the FCC and Congress in a single day. Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;http://fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;fightforthefuture.org&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 14:29:29 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-07-breaking-former-fcc-security-employee-destroys/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-08-07-breaking-former-fcc-security-employee-destroys/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>FCC now says it has no documentation of DDoS attack it claims took down website following John Oliver net neutrality segment</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;466&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;700&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/8bf2e585ae4cb043d128564aee667f18/tumblr_inline_ote94cKHc21ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;466&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;700&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 20, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;, 978-852-6457&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Agency refuses to release hundreds of pages of documents related to alleged incident. Congress must demand answers.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Federal Communications Commission (FCC) &lt;a href=&quot;http://gizmodo.com/fcc-now-says-there-is-no-documented-analysis-of-the-cyb-1797073113&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;admitted&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; last night that it has no “documented analysis” to back up its claim that a DDoS attack took down the agency’s public comment website immediately following a viral John Oliver segment about net neutrality in May. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The news comes in response to a Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) request from Gizmodo &amp;ndash; but the FCC &lt;a href=&quot;http://gizmodo.com/fcc-now-says-there-is-no-documented-analysis-of-the-cyb-1797073113&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;refused&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to release more than 200 pages of additional documents related to the alleged incident. Fight for the Future, a  nonpartisan digital rights organization that played a lead role in the massive net neutrality day of action on July 12, issued the following statement, which can be attributed to campaign director Evan Greer (pronouns: she/her):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;“At this point even supporters of Ajit Pai’s plan to gut online free speech protections have to be wondering: what is the FCC hiding? &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;This federal agency has a responsibility to maintain a functioning website for the public to comment on proceedings that have a profound impact on our economy, our democracy, and the future of the Internet. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;It’s clear that the FCC has failed to perform this basic duty, and now they are refusing to release hundreds of pages of documents that could help shed light on what really happened here, and who, if anyone, has been attempting to interfere with the public comment process.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;The public deserves to know whether former Verizon lawyer Ajit Pai is protecting the person or organization behind these alleged DDoS attacks and the flood of fake comments using stolen identities that have tainted the FCC’s docket. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Net neutrality protections protect Internet users from extra fees, censorship, and throttling. Members of Congress who oversee the FCC must demand that the agency provide adequate answers to these serious questions surrounding their comment process before they make any decision about net neutrality rules that affect hundreds of millions of Internet users.” &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future is one of the leading grassroots organizations fighting for net neutrality and Internet freedom. The group recently &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-18-net-neutrality-activists-set-sights-on-congress/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;plans to crowdfund billboards to expose members of Congress who support the FCC’s plan to dismantle net neutrality protections, and launched a scorecard to make it easy for voters to learn where their lawmakers stand on the issue. The group also played a lead role in the massive July 12 day of action &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-13-update-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;that drove&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;millions of comments, emails, and phone calls to decision makers in support of the Title II rules. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 10:48:16 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-20-fcc-now-says-it-has-no-documentation-of-ddos/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-20-fcc-now-says-it-has-no-documentation-of-ddos/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fight for the Future statement in response to White House comments on FCC plan to dismantle net neutrality free speech protections</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 18, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;News reports today indicate that the White House has offered comments regarding the FCC’s plan to slash Title II based net neutrality protections that prevent companies like Comcast and AT&amp;amp;T from charging extra fees, or engaging in throttling, offering paid fast lanes, and censorship. Digital rights group Fight for the Future, a leading net neutrality organization that played a key role in the recent massive day of action on July 12, issued the following statement, which can be attributed to campaign director, Evan Greer (pronouns: she/her):&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;“The White House’s comments today are far from full throated support for the FCC’s plan, and underscore the reality that voters from across the political spectrum, including &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.newsmax.com/Newsfront/internet-free-and-open-service-providers-conservatives/2017/07/13/id/801539/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;more than 75%&lt;/a&gt; of those who voted for Donald Trump, support strong net neutrality protections that keep the web free of extra fees, throttling, and censorship. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;FCC chairman Ajit Pai is increasingly isolated &amp;ndash; he has clearly misjudged the Republican base. No one wants companies like Comcast, Verizon, and AT&amp;amp;T to have the power to decide what we can see and what we can say on the Internet.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;The White House fell far short of supporting the FCC’s plan, and only noted that they are right to “review” the current rules. This is a clear signal that they know how unpopular the repeal of net neutrality rules is with voters, including conservatives and libertarians.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Net neutrality is the free speech fight of our generation. Internet users are outraged and paying attention. Decision makers in Washington, DC need to listen to the public, not just lobbyists from big telecom companies. When they do, they’ll realize that allowing the FCC to move forward with their plan to slash net neutrality protections will result in them being seen by constituents as enemies of the Internet, enemies of innovation, and enemies of freedom.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-18-net-neutrality-activists-set-sights-on-congress/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;announced &lt;/a&gt;this morning plans to turn its focus to Congress, with a new wave of billboards focused on lawmakers who support the FCC’s plan, and a “congressional scorecard” to make it easy for voters to learn where their members stand. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Background on the historic July 12 net neutrality day of action: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly all of the most popular websites on the web participated in a historic Internet-Wide &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/july12&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Day of Action&lt;/a&gt; to Save Net Neutrality on July 12, 2017 to oppose the FCC’s plan to slash Title II, the legal foundation for net neutrality rules that protect online free speech and innovation. A flood of web platforms small and large like Twitter, Reddit, Netflix, Spotify, 4chan, Airbnb, Amazon, Mozilla, OK Cupid, Vimeo, Tinder, Expedia, Pornhub, Imgur, Yelp, Spotify, and Soundcloud &amp;ndash; along with a vast array of online communities from every corner of the Internet: gaming forums, YouTube creators, subreddits and more &amp;ndash; displayed prominent protest messages to their users, encouraging them to take action by contacting the FCC and Congress through tools like &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BattleForTheNet.com&lt;/a&gt; that make it easy for Internet users to make their voices heard. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS, IMAGES, and DESCRIPTIONS of how participants are protesting here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;SEE A SAMPLING OF VIDEO COMMENTS here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/225341994/852009671a&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/225341994/852009671a&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was so much activity on this day that organizers are still in the process of documenting and compiling it, but here are some initial numbers showing the scale of this massive event:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tens of millions of people saw the protest messages on participating websites&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Over 5 million emails to Congress (which will be delivered over coming days)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;More than 2 million comments to the FCC (nearly tripling our Sept. 10th 2014 “Internet Slowdown” record for most in a single day)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;More than 125,000 phone calls to Congress&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;#NetNeutrality trended on both Facebook and Twitter&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Protesters went in person to more than 20 Congressional offices &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;More than 125,000 websites, people, artists, online creators, and organizations signed up to participate in the initial call to protest&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Celebrities flocked to support the effort including &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/PearlJam/status/885230542576205824&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pearl Jam&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Wilco/status/885233478719221762&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wilco&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/PearlJam/status/885230542576205824&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wil Wheaton&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/TimRobbins1/status/885154464432136192&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tim Robbins&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SusanSarandon/status/885196657792516097&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Susan Sarandon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/blues_traveler/status/885242752656605184&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Blues Traveler&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/stephenfry/status/884942083252920320&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Steven Fry&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/MarkRuffalo/status/885098668910444544&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mark Ruffalo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/LauraJaneGrace/status/885226732369960964&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Laura Jane Grace&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/kendrick38/status/885159414902042628&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Kendrick Sampson&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://consequenceofsound.net/2017/07/ted-leo-and-amanda-palmer-explain-why-we-need-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Amanda Palmer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://consequenceofsound.net/2017/07/ted-leo-and-amanda-palmer-explain-why-we-need-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ted Leo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/FullFrontalSamB/status/885257665924018176&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Samantha Bee&lt;/a&gt;, and many more.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Broad participation from every corner of the Internet: from online gaming communities to librarians to real estate sites to grassroots organizations to independent musicians. &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;See a gallery here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Facebook, Google, and Dropbox three of the largest Internet companies, came out publicly with strong statements in support of the current FCC rules. This is significant &amp;ndash; especially given Facebook’s previous opposition to certain net neutrality rules, notably in India.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effort is led by many of the grassroots groups behind the largest online protests in history including the SOPA blackout and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/infographic&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;. Media attention for online mobilizations tends to focus on the big names participating, but there is a much more interesting story: a coalition of Internet activists huddled over their laptops in coworking spaces, home offices, and coffee shops, who are the ones who came up with the idea, called for, and organized the protest, and have since been working together to lay the groundwork, build the technical tools, and create the educational resources that make it possible for large and small websites to participate in these mass days of action. It’s a grassroots effort involving dozens of volunteers working together in Slack channels, outreach spreadsheets, endless email chains, organizing in online communities and forums, and an enormous amount of creativity and digital elbow grease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The list of sites and apps participating has grown so quickly it’s almost impossible to keep up, but participants include Automattic (Wordpress), eBay, Rosetta Stone, Pinterest, Amazon, Mozilla, Netflix, Etsy, Kickstarter, Soundcloud, Dropbox, Spotify, Redfin, Facebook, Google, Snapchat, Medium, Y Combinator, GitHub, Pantheon, Opera, Bittorrent Inc., Shapeways, Nextdoor, Stack Overflow, Funny Or Die, Dreamhost, and CREDO Mobile, Goldenfrog, Fark, Chess.com, Namecheap, DuckDuckGo, Checkout.com, Sonic, Ting, ProtonMail, O’Reilly Media, SlashDot, Dribble, Dischord, SourceForge, and Union Square Ventures. Organizations participating include Fight for the Future, Free Press Action Fund, Demand Progress, Center for Media Justice, EFF,  Internet Association, Internet Archive, World Wide Web Foundation, Creative Commons, National Hispanic Media Coalition, Greenpeace, Common Cause, ACLU, Rock the Vote, American Library Association, Daily Kos, OpenMedia, The Nation, PCCC, MoveOn, OFA, Public Knowledge, OTI, Color of Change, MoveOn, Free Software Foundation, Internet Creators Guild, the Women’s March, and many others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 16:59:39 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-18-fight-for-the-future-statement-in-response-to/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-18-fight-for-the-future-statement-in-response-to/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fight for the Future Statement Regarding Incorrect Billboard Report</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 18, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This morning Fight for the Future &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-18-net-neutrality-activists-set-sights-on-congress/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;announced&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;plans to put up crowdfunded billboards focused on members of Congress who oppose net neutrality protections.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rep Scalise’s name was incorrectly included in private emails to two reporters, due to a copy paste error, and reported by Politico. This error was immediately corrected once brought to our attention, and we regret the confusion it caused. We would obviously not run billboards against someone who is in the hospital, and wish Rep Scalise a speedy recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for the billboards focused on other members, Congress plays an important role overseeing the FCC, and voters deserve to know where their members stand. The goal of our billboards is to make sure that the public knows which members are supporting the FCC’s plan to dismantle important net neutrality protections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 15:26:35 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-18-fight-for-the-future-statement-regarding-incorrect/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-18-fight-for-the-future-statement-regarding-incorrect/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Net Neutrality activists set sights on Congress: plan to unleash new wave of billboards and scorecard for lawmakers following historic day of action</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2536&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3944&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/d1e644ec92f4901d0f4bb5bd3488fd6d/tumblr_inline_otaelbVFXH1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;2536&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;3944&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 18, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;July 12 protest drove record numbers of comments, emails, and phone calls&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Digital rights group Fight for the Future unveiled today the next steps in the battle for the future of the Internet: turning the focus on Congress &amp;ndash; who have oversight over the FCC and whose actions will determine whether Ajit Pai’s unpopular plan moves forward &amp;ndash; with a wave of &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://donate.fightforthefuture.org/campaigns/nnbillboards/#page-1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;crowdfunded billboards&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;and a &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/#scoreboard&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;“congressional scorecard”&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;on BattleForTheNet.com showing where lawmakers stand. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group has already raised more than $50,000 toward the billboards, which will go up in the coming weeks targeting lawmakers who support FCC Chairman Ajit Pai’s plan to gut net neutrality rules that prevent companies like Comcast, AT&amp;amp;T, and Verizon from charging extra fees, slowing down websites, and engaging in censorship. The congressional scorecard makes it easy for voters to quickly learn their representative’s positions, and impossible for members of Congress to hide from their constituents. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See the crowdfunding page for the billboards here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://donate.fightforthefuture.org/campaigns/nnbillboards/#page-1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://donate.fightforthefuture.org/campaigns/nnbillboards/#page-1&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See the congressional scorecard here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/#scoreboard&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.battleforthenet.com/#scoreboard&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Internet users are pissed off and paying attention,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, &lt;/b&gt;“Any lawmaker that stands idly by and allows the FCC to gut these basic free speech protections that people from across the political spectrum overwhelmingly support will be seen as an enemy of the Internet and an enemy of free speech. These billboards, and the scorecard, are just the beginning.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The group plans to initially put up billboards targeting House GOP leadership members who used a meeting last week &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://thehill.com/policy/technology/341867-house-republican-leadership-cautions-tech-on-net-neutrality-report&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;to threaten&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;tech companies who were participating in the historic net neutrality day of action on July 12&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-13-update-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;which drove&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;millions of comments, emails and phone calls to decision makers, and saw broad participation from every corner of the Internet from major web platforms, startups, YouTubers, gamers, and forums like 4chan and reddit. The billboards will also mention lawmakers vote to gut Internet privacy rules that prevent ISPs from collecting and selling customer information to advertisers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/#scoreboard&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;congressional scorecard&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;divides Congress into two camps: Team Internet (those who are speaking up to defend net neutrality rules that protect online free speech) and Team Cable (those who are supporting the FCC’s plan to dismantle those protections and give Cable companies control over our online experience.) Lawmakers on “Team Cable” should expect to be targeted with billboards in the coming weeks if they do not speak out against Ajit Pai’s plan. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The announcements of both the billboards and scorecard come as all eyes shift to the Senate where Ajit Pai is expected to be confirmed as commissioner this week in a largely procedural vote. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Background on the historic July 12 net neutrality day of action: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly all of the most popular websites on the web participated in a historic Internet-Wide &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/july12&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Day of Action&lt;/a&gt; to Save Net Neutrality on July 12, 2017 to oppose the FCC’s plan to slash Title II, the legal foundation for net neutrality rules that protect online free speech and innovation. A flood of web platforms small and large like Twitter, Reddit, Netflix, Spotify, 4chan, Airbnb, Amazon, Mozilla, OK Cupid, Vimeo, Tinder, Expedia, Pornhub, Imgur, Yelp, Spotify, and Soundcloud &amp;ndash; along with a vast array of online communities from every corner of the Internet: gaming forums, YouTube creators, subreddits and more &amp;ndash; displayed prominent protest messages to their users, encouraging them to take action by contacting the FCC and Congress through tools like &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BattleForTheNet.com&lt;/a&gt; that make it easy for Internet users to make their voices heard. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS, IMAGES, and DESCRIPTIONS of how participants are protesting here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;SEE A SAMPLING OF VIDEO COMMENTS here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/225341994/852009671a&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/225341994/852009671a&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was so much activity on this day that organizers are still in the process of documenting and compiling it, but here are some initial numbers showing the scale of this massive event:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tens of millions of people saw the protest messages on participating websites&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Over 5 million emails to Congress (which will be delivered over coming days)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;More than 2 million comments to the FCC (nearly tripling our Sept. 10th 2014 “Internet Slowdown” record for most in a single day)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;More than 125,000 phone calls to Congress&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;#NetNeutrality trended on both Facebook and Twitter&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Protesters went in person to more than 20 Congressional offices &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;More than 125,000 websites, people, artists, online creators, and organizations signed up to participate in the initial call to protest&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Celebrities flocked to support the effort including &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/PearlJam/status/885230542576205824&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pearl Jam&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Wilco/status/885233478719221762&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wilco&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/PearlJam/status/885230542576205824&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wil Wheaton&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/TimRobbins1/status/885154464432136192&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tim Robbins&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SusanSarandon/status/885196657792516097&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Susan Sarandon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/blues_traveler/status/885242752656605184&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Blues Traveler&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/stephenfry/status/884942083252920320&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Steven Fry&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/MarkRuffalo/status/885098668910444544&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mark Ruffalo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/LauraJaneGrace/status/885226732369960964&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Laura Jane Grace&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/kendrick38/status/885159414902042628&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Kendrick Sampson&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://consequenceofsound.net/2017/07/ted-leo-and-amanda-palmer-explain-why-we-need-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Amanda Palmer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://consequenceofsound.net/2017/07/ted-leo-and-amanda-palmer-explain-why-we-need-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ted Leo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/FullFrontalSamB/status/885257665924018176&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Samantha Bee&lt;/a&gt;, and many more.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Broad participation from every corner of the Internet: from online gaming communities to librarians to real estate sites to grassroots organizations to independent musicians. &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;See a gallery here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Facebook, Google, and Dropbox three of the largest Internet companies, came out publicly with strong statements in support of the current FCC rules. This is significant &amp;ndash; especially given Facebook’s previous opposition to certain net neutrality rules, notably in India.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effort is led by many of the grassroots groups behind the largest online protests in history including the SOPA blackout and the&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/infographic&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/b&gt;Media attention for online mobilizations tends to focus on the big names participating, but there is a much more interesting story: a coalition of Internet activists huddled over their laptops in coworking spaces, home offices, and coffee shops, who are the ones who came up with the idea, called for, and organized the protest, and have since been working together to lay the groundwork, build the technical tools, and create the educational resources that make it possible for large and small websites to participate in these mass days of action. It’s a grassroots effort involving dozens of volunteers working together in Slack channels, outreach spreadsheets, endless email chains, organizing in online communities and forums, and an enormous amount of creativity and digital elbow grease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The list of sites and apps participating has grown so quickly it’s almost impossible to keep up, but participants include Automattic (Wordpress), eBay, Rosetta Stone, Pinterest, Amazon, Mozilla, Netflix, Etsy, Kickstarter, Soundcloud, Dropbox, Spotify, Redfin, Facebook, Google, Snapchat, Medium, Y Combinator, GitHub, Pantheon, Opera, Bittorrent Inc., Shapeways, Nextdoor, Stack Overflow, Funny Or Die, Dreamhost, and CREDO Mobile, Goldenfrog, Fark, Chess.com, Namecheap, DuckDuckGo, Checkout.com, Sonic, Ting, ProtonMail, O’Reilly Media, SlashDot, Dribble, Dischord, SourceForge, and Union Square Ventures. Organizations participating include Fight for the Future, Free Press Action Fund, Demand Progress, Center for Media Justice, EFF,  Internet Association, Internet Archive, World Wide Web Foundation, Creative Commons, National Hispanic Media Coalition, Greenpeace, Common Cause, ACLU, Rock the Vote, American Library Association, Daily Kos, OpenMedia, The Nation, PCCC, MoveOn, OFA, Public Knowledge, OTI, Color of Change, MoveOn, Free Software Foundation, Internet Creators Guild, the Women’s March, and many others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 08:57:56 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-18-net-neutrality-activists-set-sights-on-congress/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-18-net-neutrality-activists-set-sights-on-congress/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UPDATE: Historic day of action for Net Neutrality breaks records: more than 2 million comments to FCC, millions of emails and phone calls to Congress</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;vimeo&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fvimeo.com%2F225341994%2F852009671a&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/225341994?title=0&amp;amp;byline=0&amp;amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 13, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;More than 125,000 websites, Internet users, and organizations participated in a massive online protest against the FCC’s plan to gut protections that keep the web free from censorship, throttling, and extra fees. Protesters gathered in DC and showed up at Congressional district offices, celebs weigh in&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly all of the most popular websites on the web participated in a historic Internet-Wide &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/july12&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Day of Action&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to Save Net Neutrality yesterday to oppose the FCC’s plan to slash Title II, the legal foundation for net neutrality rules that protect online free speech and innovation. A flood of web platforms small and large like Twitter, Reddit, Netflix, Spotify, 4chan, Airbnb, Amazon, Mozilla, OK Cupid, Vimeo, Tinder, Expedia, Pornhub, Imgur, Yelp, Spotify, and Soundcloud &amp;ndash; along with a vast array of online communities from every corner of the Internet: gaming forums, YouTube creators, subreddits and more &amp;ndash; displayed prominent protest messages to their users, encouraging them to take action by contacting the FCC and Congress through tools like &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BattleForTheNet.com&lt;/a&gt; that make it easy for Internet users to make their voices heard. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS, IMAGES, and DESCRIPTIONS of how participants are protesting here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;SEE A SAMPLING OF VIDEO COMMENTS here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://vimeo.com/225341994/852009671a&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://vimeo.com/225341994/852009671a&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There has been such a surge in activity &amp;ndash; and the traffic is STILL coming in &amp;ndash; that organizers are still scrambling to document everything that has happened but so far through the BattleForTheNet.com site alone (not including the Internet Association’s page or other aligned efforts) we’ve seen:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;IMPORTANT NOTE: these numbers STILL represent only a portion of the final totals, and due to the massive numbers, comments and emails will be delivered over several days.  We will release additional updates as we continue documenting what has happened:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tens of millions of people saw the protest messages on participating websites&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Over 5 million emails to Congress &lt;/b&gt;(which will be delivered over coming days)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;More than 2 million comments to the FCC&lt;/b&gt; (nearly tripling our Sept. 10th 2014 “Internet Slowdown” record for most in a single day)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;124,000 phone calls to Congress&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;#NetNeutrality trended on both Facebook and Twitter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Protesters &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/Zkop6&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;went in person&lt;/a&gt; to more than 20 Congressional offices &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;More than 125,000 websites, people, artists, online creators, and organizations&lt;/b&gt; signed up to participate in the initial call to protest&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Celebrities flocked to support the effort &lt;/b&gt;including &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/PearlJam/status/885230542576205824&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pearl Jam&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/Wilco/status/885233478719221762&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wilco&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/PearlJam/status/885230542576205824&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wil Wheaton&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/TimRobbins1/status/885154464432136192&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tim Robbins&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SusanSarandon/status/885196657792516097&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Susan Sarandon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/blues_traveler/status/885242752656605184&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Blues Traveler&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/stephenfry/status/884942083252920320&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Steven Fry&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/MarkRuffalo/status/885098668910444544&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mark Ruffalo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/LauraJaneGrace/status/885226732369960964&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Laura Jane Grace&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/kendrick38/status/885159414902042628&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Kendrick Sampson&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://consequenceofsound.net/2017/07/ted-leo-and-amanda-palmer-explain-why-we-need-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Amanda Palmer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://consequenceofsound.net/2017/07/ted-leo-and-amanda-palmer-explain-why-we-need-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ted Leo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/FullFrontalSamB/status/885257665924018176&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Samantha Bee&lt;/a&gt;, and many more.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Broad participation from every corner of the Internet:&lt;/b&gt; from online gaming communities to librarians to real estate sites to grassroots organizations to independent musicians. &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;See a gallery here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE: The volume of participation was so high that the FCC has been “rate limiting” submissions into their docket&lt;/b&gt; &amp;ndash; there are an enormous number of comments queued up that will be submitted into their system before the July 17 deadline, as fast as their system can handle them. The same is true for emails to Congress members, which will be delivered in the days to come.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Facebook, Google, and Dropbox&lt;/b&gt; three of the largest Internet companies, came out publicly with strong statements in support of the current FCC rules. This is significant &amp;ndash; especially given Facebook’s previous opposition to certain net neutrality rules, notably in India.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, one of the leading groups behind the protest, issued the following statement (pronouns: she/hers): &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This was a historic moment when the Internet is realizing it’s power—with massive amounts of creative activism spreading to every corner of the Internet, from the smallest and weirdest nooks and crannies of the web to the most popular websites on earth. And this doesn’t end today—this protest is the kickoff of a sustained campaign to keep the pressure on lawmakers and the FCC to do the right thing. This is just our opening salvo, and it’s a massive one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The FCC needs to listen to the public, not just lobbyists from big cable companies. No one wants companies like Comcast, AT&amp;amp;T, and Verizon to have control over what we can see and do online, or to have to pay them extra fees to access the content we want. The Internet is outraged by censorship and corruption, this is our moment to to defend net neutrality and fight for the future of freedom of expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Lawmakers in Washington, DC need to understand that if they stand idly by and allow the FCC to gut these rules that are overwhelmingly supported by voters from across the political spectrum, they will be seen as enemies of the Internet and enemies of free speech.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pierce Stanley, technology fellow at Demand Progress, which co-led the effort: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Today, the largest web platforms in the world, scrappy activist organizations, and individuals from across the political spectrum came together online and in-person to make their voices heard. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Americans took to the internet to stand up for the rights to communicate freely, to organize, and to innovate online.  Ajit Pai’s plan to undermine net neutrality and stifle online speech would endanger these ways we use the internet, and could even make it harder &amp;ndash; or impossible &amp;ndash; to organize protests like today’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Ajit Pai may think big cable’s interests are more important than the public’s, but today’s activism makes it clear that few outside the boardrooms of Comcast or AT&amp;amp;T agree. A large majority of Americans of all political persuasions support net neutrality, and their voices were heard loud and clear. Today was the first step in taking back the internet from Pai and his cable cabal.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Candace Clement, campaign director for Free Press Action Fund, which co-led the effort:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People used the internet to save the internet today. That’s because the Trump FCC’s push to ​destroy​ ​Net Neutrality's​ ​legal foundation​ ​isn&amp;rsquo;t fooling anyone​. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“We know that the open internet is critical for marginalized communities that ​​corporate media have misrepresented; that it’s essential for free speech and political organizing online; and that tech entrepreneurs need an open network to survive just as much as working families​ do​. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“Today we all joined together to stop FCC Chairman Pai’s quest to destroy the Net Neutrality safeguards that are ​crucial​ to everyone’s right to connect and communicate. And we’re going to stick with this fight for as long as it takes to preserve the open internet protections the majority of Americans demand.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Malkia Cyril, executive director of the Center for Media Justice which co-led the effort, said:&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Today, thousands of people of color and civil rights leaders raised our voices to say loud and clear: we won&amp;rsquo;t let our internet become like cable TV, a white, middle class, and male bastion where we are shouted down daily. We&amp;rsquo;ll keep joining with allies of all kinds across the lines of difference to fight for our digital voice, and ensure that an open Internet protected by Title II net neutrality delivers political power and economic opportunity for those long excluded from both. The stakes are too high to do anything less.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effort is led by many of the grassroots groups behind the largest online protests in history including the SOPA blackout and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/infographic&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;. Media attention for online mobilizations tends to focus on the big names participating, but there is a much more interesting story: a coalition of Internet activists huddled over their laptops in coworking spaces, home offices, and coffee shops, who are the ones who came up with the idea, called for, and organized the protest, and have since been working together to lay the groundwork, build the technical tools, and create the educational resources that make it possible for large and small websites to participate in these mass days of action. It’s a grassroots effort involving dozens of volunteers working together in Slack channels, outreach spreadsheets, endless email chains, organizing in online communities and forums, and an enormous amount of creativity and digital elbow grease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The list of sites and apps participating has grown so quickly it’s almost impossible to keep up, but participants include Automattic (Wordpress), eBay, Rosetta Stone, Pinterest, Amazon, Mozilla, Netflix, Etsy, Kickstarter, Soundcloud, Dropbox, Spotify, Redfin, Facebook, Google, Snapchat, Medium, Y Combinator, GitHub, Pantheon, Opera, Bittorrent Inc., Shapeways, Nextdoor, Stack Overflow, Funny Or Die, Dreamhost, and CREDO Mobile, Goldenfrog, Fark, Chess.com, Namecheap, DuckDuckGo, Checkout.com, Sonic, Ting, ProtonMail, O’Reilly Media, SlashDot, Dribble, Dischord, SourceForge, and Union Square Ventures. Organizations participating include Fight for the Future, Free Press Action Fund, Demand Progress, Center for Media Justice, EFF,  Internet Association, Internet Archive, World Wide Web Foundation, Creative Commons, National Hispanic Media Coalition, Greenpeace, Common Cause, ACLU, Rock the Vote, American Library Association, Daily Kos, OpenMedia, The Nation, PCCC, MoveOn, OFA, Public Knowledge, OTI, Color of Change, MoveOn, Free Software Foundation, Internet Creators Guild, the Women’s March, and many others.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 12:01:37 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-13-update-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-13-update-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Historic day of action for Net Neutrality breaks records: more than 1.6 million comments heading to FCC, 3 million+ emails and phone calls to Congress, well over 10 million people reached so far, as of 7:00pm</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;748&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1399&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/eba973f468853ba9a79db6aaec538e4a/tumblr_inline_ot02v7QZop1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;748&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1399&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 12, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;More than 125,000 websites, Internet users, and organizations are participating in a massive online protest against the FCC’s plan to gut protections that keep the web free from censorship, throttling, and extra fees. Protesters gathering in DC and other cities, celebs weigh in&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of the most popular websites on the web have been participating in a historic Internet-Wide &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/july12&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Day of Action&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;to Save Net Neutrality today to oppose the FCC’s plan to slash Title II, the legal foundation for net neutrality rules that protect online free speech and innovation. A flood of major web platforms like Twitter, Reddit, Netflix, Spotify, 4chan, Airbnb, Amazon, Mozilla, OK Cupid, Vimeo, Tinder, Expedia, Pornhub, Imgur, Yelp, and Soundcloud displayed prominent protest messages to their users, encouraging them to take action by contacting the FCC and Congress through tools like &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BattleForTheNet.com&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;that make it easy for Internet users to make their voices heard. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS, IMAGES, and DESCRIPTIONS of how participants are protesting here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There has been such a surge in activity &amp;ndash; and the traffic is not showing signs of slowing down &amp;ndash; that organizers are still scrambling to document everything that has happened but so far through the BattleForTheNet.com site alone (not including the Internet Association’s page or other aligned efforts) we’ve seen:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;IMPORTANT NOTE: these numbers represent only a portion of the final totals, and due to the massive numbers, comments and emails will be delivered over several days.  We will release additional updates as we continue documenting what has happened:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Well over 10 million people saw the protest messages&lt;/b&gt; on participating websites&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;3,450,000+ emails to Congress&lt;/b&gt; (which will be delivered over coming days)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;More than 1.6 million comments to the FCC&lt;/b&gt; (breaking our Sept. 10th 2014 “Internet Slowdown” record for most in a single day)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;#NetNeutrality trended on both Facebook and Twitter&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;More than 125,000 websites, people, artists, online creators, and organizations signed up to participate&lt;/b&gt; in the initial call to protest&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Celebrities flocked to support the effort &lt;/b&gt;including &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/PearlJam/status/885230542576205824&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Pearl Jam&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/PearlJam/status/885230542576205824&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wil Wheaton&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/TimRobbins1/status/885154464432136192&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tim Robbins&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SusanSarandon/status/885196657792516097&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Susan Sarandon&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/blues_traveler/status/885242752656605184&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Blues Traveler&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/stephenfry/status/884942083252920320&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Steven Fry&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/MarkRuffalo/status/885098668910444544&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mark Ruffalo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/LauraJaneGrace/status/885226732369960964&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Laura Jane Grace&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/kendrick38/status/885159414902042628&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Kendrick Sampson&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://consequenceofsound.net/2017/07/ted-leo-and-amanda-palmer-explain-why-we-need-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Amanda Palmer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://consequenceofsound.net/2017/07/ted-leo-and-amanda-palmer-explain-why-we-need-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ted Leo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/FullFrontalSamB/status/885257665924018176&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Samantha Bee&lt;/a&gt;, and many more.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Broad participation from every corner of the Internet:&lt;/b&gt; from online gaming communities to librarians to real estate sites to grassroots organizations to independent musicians.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;NOTE: The volume of participation was so high that the FCC has been “rate limiting” submissions into their docket &amp;ndash; there are an enormous number of comments queued up that will be submitted into their system before the July 17 deadline, as fast as their system can handle them. The same is true for emails to Congress members, which will be delivered in the days to come.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Embed a video about the day of action here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DcIFBb3e3tFA%26feature%3Dyoutu.be&amp;amp;t=MGY2YThjMzU5MTMyMWQzMzEwNmVkYzk4ZmUyODViZTBmMDA1NzgxZixBdTdLV0dLRA%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F162821217028%2Flargest-websites-on-earth-prepare-for-net&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cIFBb3e3tFA&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More highlights in this Twitter moment: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/i/moments/885130181039579136&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/i/moments/885130181039579136&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, one of the leading groups behind the protest, issued the following statement (pronouns: she/hers): &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“Today is a historic moment when the Internet is realizing it’s power—with massive amounts of creative activism spreading to every corner of the Internet, from the smallest and weirdest nooks and crannies of the web to the most popular websites on earth. And this doesn’t end today—this protest is the kickoff of a sustained campaign to keep the pressure on lawmakers and the FCC to do the right thing. This is just our opening salvo, and it’s a massive one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The FCC needs to listen to the public, not just lobbyists from big cable companies. No one wants companies like Comcast, AT&amp;amp;T, and Verizon to have control over what we can see and do online, or to have to pay them extra fees to access the content we want. The Internet is outraged by censorship and corruption, this is our moment to to defend net neutrality and fight for the future of freedom of expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Lawmakers in Washington, DC need to understand that if they stand idly by and allow the FCC to gut these rules that are overwhelmingly supported by voters from across the political spectrum, they will be seen as enemies of the Internet and enemies of free speech.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Pierce Stanley, technology fellow at Demand Progress, which co-led the effort: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Today, the largest web platforms in the world, scrappy activist organizations, and individuals from across the political spectrum came together online and in-person to make their voices heard. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Americans took to the internet to stand up for the rights to communicate freely, to organize, and to innovate online.  Ajit Pai’s plan to undermine net neutrality and stifle online speech would endanger these ways we use the internet, and could even make it harder &amp;ndash; or impossible &amp;ndash; to organize protests like today’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Ajit Pai may think big cable’s interests are more important than the public’s, but today’s activism makes it clear that few outside the boardrooms of Comcast or AT&amp;amp;T agree. A large majority of Americans of all political persuasions support net neutrality, and their voices were heard loud and clear. Today was the first step in taking back the internet from Pai and his cable cabal.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Candace Clement, campaign director for Free Press Action Fund, which co-led the effort:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“People used the internet to save the internet today. That’s because the Trump FCC’s push to ​destroy​ ​Net Neutrality's​ ​legal foundation​ ​isn&amp;rsquo;t fooling anyone​. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“We know that the open internet is critical for marginalized communities that ​​corporate media have misrepresented; that it’s essential for free speech and political organizing online; and that tech entrepreneurs need an open network to survive just as much as working families​ do​. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;“Today we all joined together to stop FCC Chairman Pai’s quest to destroy the Net Neutrality safeguards that are ​crucial​ to everyone’s right to connect and communicate. And we’re going to stick with this fight for as long as long as it takes to preserve the open internet protections the majority of Americans demand.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Malkia Cyril, executive director of the Center for Media Justice which co-led the effort, said:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Today, thousands of people of color and civil rights leaders raised our voices to say loud and clear: we won&amp;rsquo;t let our internet become like cable TV, a white, middle class, and male bastion where we are shouted down daily. We&amp;rsquo;ll keep joining with allies of all kinds across the lines of difference to fight for our digital voice, and ensure that an open Internet protected by Title II net neutrality delivers political power and economic opportunity for those long excluded from both. The stakes are too high to do anything less.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effort is led by many of the grassroots groups behind the largest online protests in history including the SOPA blackout and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/infographic&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;. Media attention for online mobilizations tends to focus on the big names participating, but there is a much more interesting story: a coalition of Internet activists huddled over their laptops in coworking spaces, home offices, and coffee shops, who are the ones who came up with the idea, called for, and organized the protest, and have since been working together to lay the groundwork, build the technical tools, and create the educational resources that make it possible for large and small websites to participate in these mass days of action. It’s a grassroots effort involving dozens of volunteers working together in Slack channels, outreach spreadsheets, endless email chains, organizing in online communities and forums, and an enormous amount of creativity and digital elbow grease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The list of sites and apps participating has grown so quickly it’s almost impossible to keep up, but participants include Automattic (Wordpress), eBay, Rosetta Stone, Pinterest, Amazon, Mozilla, Netflix, Etsy, Kickstarter, Soundcloud, Dropbox, Spotify, Redfin, Facebook, Google, Snapchat, Medium, Y Combinator, GitHub, Pantheon, Opera, Bittorrent Inc., Shapeways, Nextdoor, Stack Overflow, Funny Or Die, Dreamhost, and CREDO Mobile, Goldenfrog, Fark, Chess.com, Namecheap, DuckDuckGo, Checkout.com, Sonic, Ting, ProtonMail, O’Reilly Media, SlashDot, Dribble, Dischord, SourceForge, and Union Square Ventures. Organizations participating include Fight for the Future, Free Press Action Fund, Demand Progress, Center for Media Justice, EFF,  Internet Association, Internet Archive, World Wide Web Foundation, Creative Commons, National Hispanic Media Coalition, Greenpeace, Common Cause, ACLU, Rock the Vote, American Library Association, Daily Kos, OpenMedia, The Nation, PCCC, MoveOn, OFA, Public Knowledge, OTI, Color of Change, MoveOn, Free Software Foundation, Internet Creators Guild, the Women’s March, and many others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 19:06:46 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-12-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality-breaks/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-12-historic-day-of-action-for-net-neutrality-breaks/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>UPDATE: Massive protest for net neutrality spreads across the Internet</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;713&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1357&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/eea02c4afd6799a15e47559f1e434ee2/tumblr_inline_oszpcmyZlK1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;713&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1357&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 12, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;More than 100,000  websites, Internet users, and organizations are participating in a massive online protest against the FCC’s plan to gut protections that keep the web free from censorship, throttling, and extra fees. Protesters have also gathered outside the Senate in DC.&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of the most popular websites on the web are participating in an Internet-Wide &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/july12&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Day of Action&lt;/a&gt; to Save Net Neutrality today to oppose the FCC’s plan to slash Title II, the legal foundation for net neutrality rules that protect online free speech and innovation. Starting at midnight, a flood of major web platforms like Twitter, Reddit, Netflix, Spotify, Airbnb, Amazon, Mozilla, OK Cupid, Vimeo, Pornhub, Imgur, and Soundcloud began displaying prominent protest messages to their users, encouraging them to take action by contacting the FCC and Congress through tools like &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BattleForTheNet.com&lt;/a&gt; that make it easy for Internet users to make their voices heard. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See PHOTOS, IMAGES, and DESCRIPTIONS of how participants are protesting here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;http://imgur.com/a/vYVet&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Embed a video about the day of action here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DcIFBb3e3tFA%26feature%3Dyoutu.be&amp;amp;t=MGY2YThjMzU5MTMyMWQzMzEwNmVkYzk4ZmUyODViZTBmMDA1NzgxZixBdTdLV0dLRA%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F162821217028%2Flargest-websites-on-earth-prepare-for-net&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cIFBb3e3tFA&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;More highlights in this Twitter moment: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/i/moments/885130181039579136&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/i/moments/885130181039579136&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, one of the leading groups behind the protest, issued the following statement (pronouns: she/hers): &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;i&gt;“Today is a historic moment when the Internet is realizing it’s power. We’re massive amounts of creativity and action coming from every corner of the Internet, from the smallest and weirdest nooks and crannies of the web to the most popular websites on earth. And this doesn’t end today &amp;ndash; this protest is the kickoff of a sustained campaign to keep the pressure on lawmakers and the FCC to do the right thing. This is our opening salvo, and it’s a massive one.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;The FCC needs to listen to the public, not just lobbyists from big cable companies. Today, the Internet is showing its political power. No one wants companies like Comcast, AT&amp;amp;T, and Verizon to have control over what we can see and do online, or to have to pay them extra fees to access the content we want. The Internet is outraged by censorship and corruption, this is our moment to to defend net neutrality and fight for the future of freedom of expression.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Lawmakers in Washington, DC need to understand that if they stand idly by and allow the FCC to gut these rules that are overwhelmingly supported by voters from across the political spectrum, they will be seen as enemies of the Internet and enemies of free speech.”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;480&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;640&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/1d2d99b4cdc180fb589fe7f674100b44/tumblr_inline_oszpd6HBJG1ri3xd7_540.jpg&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;480&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;640&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 100,000 people, sites, and organizations signed up to participate the effort ahead of the 12th, and many times that will have joined in by the end of the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effort is led by many of the grassroots groups behind the largest online protests in history including the SOPA blackout and the &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/infographic&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Slowdown&lt;/a&gt;. Media attention for online mobilizations tends to focus on the big names participating, but there is a much more interesting story: a coalition of Internet activists huddled over their laptops in coworking spaces, home offices, and coffee shops, who are the ones who came up with the idea, called for, and organized the protest, and have since been working together to lay the groundwork, build the technical tools, and create the educational resources that make it possible for large and small websites to participate in these mass days of action. It’s a grassroots effort involving dozens of volunteers working together in Slack channels, outreach spreadsheets, endless email chains, organizing in online communities and forums, and an enormous amount of creativity and digital elbow grease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;928&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1604&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/20d443c348116b62168ec81dbb8bb7e2/tumblr_inline_oszpdo9Wd11ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;928&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1604&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The list of sites and apps participating has grown so quickly it’s almost impossible to keep up, but participants include Automattic (Wordpress), eBay, Rosetta Stone, Pinterest, Amazon, Mozilla, Netflix, Etsy, Kickstarter, Soundcloud, Dropbox, Spotify, Facebook, Google, Snapchat, Medium, Y Combinator, GitHub, Pantheon, Opera, Bittorrent Inc., Shapeways, Nextdoor, Stack Overflow, Funny Or Die, Dreamhost, and CREDO Mobile, Goldenfrog, Fark, Chess.com, Namecheap, DuckDuckGo, Checkout.com, Sonic, Ting, ProtonMail, O’Reilly Media, SlashDot, Dribble, Dischord, SourceForge, and Union Square Ventures. Organizations participating include Fight for the Future, Free Press Action Fund, Demand Progress, Center for Media Justice, EFF,  Internet Association, Internet Archive, World Wide Web Foundation, Creative Commons, National Hispanic Media Coalition, Greenpeace, Common Cause, ACLU, Rock the Vote, American Library Association, Daily Kos, OpenMedia, The Nation, PCCC, MoveOn, OFA, Public Knowledge, OTI, Color of Change, MoveOn, Free Software Foundation, Internet Creators Guild, the Women’s March, and many others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;925&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1501&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/8c2f6784606f30bdc4ca8584dacf20cf/tumblr_inline_oszpexGaNV1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;925&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1501&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 07:21:28 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-12-update-massive-protest-for-net-neutrality-spreads/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-12-update-massive-protest-for-net-neutrality-spreads/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to stand up for #NetNeutrality on Tumblr</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;On July 12, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.battleforthenet.com/july12/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;tons of websites&lt;/a&gt; are taking action to defend net neutrality. Here&amp;rsquo;s how to join in on Tumblr, by running this epic widget on your site.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1546&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1356&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/e80b2c3465468022c01fd8c414e92a21/tumblr_inline_osy9cvun5R1r1kl7d_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1546&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1356&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, if you&amp;rsquo;re not sure why this matters so much, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nZEw_6Y0hhU&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;watch this short and sweet video&lt;/a&gt;, and then visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://BattlefortheNet.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BattlefortheNet.com&lt;/a&gt; to contact Congress and the FCC yourself.&lt;/p&gt;Then, if you&amp;rsquo;re technically inclined, &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/fightforthefuture/battleforthenet-widget&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;check it out on Github&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re not, easy instructions (with pictures) follow:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 18:56:06 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-11-how-to-stand-up-for-netneutrality-on-tumblr/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-11-how-to-stand-up-for-netneutrality-on-tumblr/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here’s how you can participate in Net Neutrality Day if you don’t run a website.</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;p&gt;On Wednesday, July 12, &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.battleforthenet.com%2Fjuly12%2F&amp;amp;t=NzE0OTQwZTBhMDQ4NGNhZjI5Mjk3YjJiOWNmYzEyZTA3NDVkMTEyZCxBWVBuS3M2Rg%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AYQASxsD1vq-mDlMoCKwRMQ&amp;amp;p=https%3A%2F%2Ffftf-staff.tumblr.com%2Fpost%2F162872739994%2Fheres-how-you-can-participate-in-net-neutrality&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;hundreds of websites&lt;/a&gt;, including some of the biggest in the world, are taking action to alert the Internet about Big Cable’s attempt to end net neutrality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But everyone has a part to play in saving net neutrality, not just big websites.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have a Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, or any other social media account, you can use it to get your friends to join you in sending a pro-net neutrality comment to the FCC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Change your profile image&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;On Twitter the easiest way to change your profile image is to &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=https%3A%2F%2Ftwibbon.com%2FSupport%2Fsave-net-neutrality-3%23&amp;amp;t=OGE4ODcxY2Q2MmQ2NTdiODk3MzU5NmIwN2RmZDZiODYyZmY1MjA4OCxBWVBuS3M2Rg%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AYQASxsD1vq-mDlMoCKwRMQ&amp;amp;p=https%3A%2F%2Ffftf-staff.tumblr.com%2Fpost%2F162872739994%2Fheres-how-you-can-participate-in-net-neutrality&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;use our custom Twibbon&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For everywhere else, you can download one of the profile images we have designed. Simply right-click on the images below and select “Save image as…” to download. Then upload as your new profile image.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1200&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1200&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/d47a0416c924cb47dbc9ce616cde9319/tumblr_inline_osxzbhVW7d1up8o7g_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1200&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1200&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1200&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1200&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/245f6f77abb84756826998081264be70/tumblr_inline_osxzc6aziN1up8o7g_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1200&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1200&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;400&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;400&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/a5a5b3fdbf34ab7d12c9c86a3284232a/tumblr_inline_osymrpFXh51up8o7g_540.gif&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;400&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;400&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1200&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1200&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/0fc3976fab6e17644310d2c78a14977e/tumblr_inline_osxzcmjPPu1up8o7g_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1200&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1200&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many more profile image options can be found &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.dropbox.com%2Fsh%2Fhatbvjwftjgwjnm%2FAADMls0e4JJ_QGcoqbg0zNAEa%3Fdl%3D0&amp;amp;t=OTFhNWRlMGE2MWZjNmZlMDcyOTViYmYyMTA3YjQzYjNkNTEwZjI2MCxBWVBuS3M2Rg%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AYQASxsD1vq-mDlMoCKwRMQ&amp;amp;p=https%3A%2F%2Ffftf-staff.tumblr.com%2Fpost%2F162872739994%2Fheres-how-you-can-participate-in-net-neutrality&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Post a meme&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our volunteers have been busy making net neutrality memes. Post one of these to your Facebook or Instagram and &lt;b&gt;make sure to link people to &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;www.battleforthenet.com&lt;/a&gt; to take action.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Right-click on the images below to download.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;800&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;800&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/1338b1104741702540515f27a4369382/tumblr_inline_osxzia16bH1up8o7g_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;800&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;800&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;910&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;900&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/4d94f9afca27dd6737990076eeb5834b/tumblr_inline_osxzhwkPFp1up8o7g_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;910&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;900&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;700&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;708&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/611fcc6811ac59abc289b79e3264b097/tumblr_inline_osxzhk2Apm1up8o7g_540.gif&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;700&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;708&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1000&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1000&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/a23bf4b71af75dc29e00207d170987bf/tumblr_inline_osxzhfg06t1up8o7g_540.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1000&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1000&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;360&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;202&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/21e0de2435e34be635b1681948fa81e2/tumblr_inline_osxzh6uyBN1up8o7g_540.gif&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;360&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;202&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Tweet!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Post a tweet about net neutrality and urge your followers to take action. You can come up something creative about how the Internet will suffer if Big Cable gets to slow down or block sites, but here are some samples you can use for inspiration:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. Stop the FCC’s plan for throttling, blocking, &amp;amp; new fees online. Take action now to defend #NetNeutrality: battleforthenet.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. We deserve equal access to the internet &amp;amp; the FCC is trying to take that away. Act now to save #NetNeutrality: battleforthenet.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;3. This tweet is being ████ by Comcast. Well, not yet. But, only if you ████ stop them: battleforthenet.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;4. This tweet is being ████ by your internet service provider. Well, not yet. But, only if you ████ stop them: battleforthenet.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;5. #NetNeutrality preserves the freedom of information we all enjoy online. Say no to internet censorship: battleforthenet.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;6. #NetNeutrality stops internet service providers from charging extra fees. Let’s save it! Take action now: battleforthenet.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;7. #NetNeutrality stops Comcast &amp;amp; Verizon from charging extra fees. Let’s save it! Take action now: battleforthenet.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;8.  If you’re reading this, you have to act now to defend the free and open Internet. Submit your comment to the FCC at BattlefortheNet.com!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;9.  ISPs like @Comcast want 🇺🇸 to let them 🐢 the Internet for 💰. But we can 🛑 them: Battleforthenet.com #NetNeutrality&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;10.  #NetNeutrality is the First Amendment of the internet. Take action now to stop Big Cable from destroying it: battleforthenet.com&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt;Use our video bumper&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;We made a &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=https%3A%2F%2Fvimeo.com%2F223515967&amp;amp;t=NTcxZDgzODQ4ZjBiMzI5ZWU1NWFmZTYzZjc0OTU4YTU0ZjE5M2Q0MyxBWVBuS3M2Rg%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AYQASxsD1vq-mDlMoCKwRMQ&amp;amp;p=https%3A%2F%2Ffftf-staff.tumblr.com%2Fpost%2F162872739994%2Fheres-how-you-can-participate-in-net-neutrality&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;short video reel&lt;/a&gt; that explains why net neutrality matters, and how Internet users can tell the FCC and Congress to protect the open web at all costs through BattleForTheNet.com.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are square, vertical, and horizontal versions of the bumper &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=https%3A%2F%2Fdrive.google.com%2Fdrive%2Ffolders%2F0B7iKho2OIeVzY1FKTlAzS1NOVTg&amp;amp;t=YzdiMWQ4Yjk5MThlOWRkNzEzYTU0M2Y5N2E1ZDZkZTdlODJkNGU0MCxBWVBuS3M2Rg%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AYQASxsD1vq-mDlMoCKwRMQ&amp;amp;p=https%3A%2F%2Ffftf-staff.tumblr.com%2Fpost%2F162872739994%2Fheres-how-you-can-participate-in-net-neutrality&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;for you to download here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Add this reel to your online creations on or before July 12. Tell your viewers about the day of action on YouTube, Vimeo, or wherever else you host content!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-embed tmblr-full&quot; data-provider=&quot;vimeo&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;540&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;304&quot; data-url=&quot;https%3A%2F%2Fvimeo.com%2F223515967&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/223515967?title=0&amp;amp;byline=0&amp;amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;540&quot; height=&quot;304&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; title=&quot;Battle For The Net Video Bumper&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 16:02:19 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-11-heres-how-you-can-participate-in-net-neutrality/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-11-heres-how-you-can-participate-in-net-neutrality/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Largest websites on earth prepare for net neutrality day of action on July 12: Snapchat, Airbnb, Spotify, Yelp, Dropbox latest to join</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1479&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;753&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/62a07a02a1885ffb3d6fff545a55fd89/tumblr_inline_osxcr2lxUX1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1479&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;753&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 10, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;More than 80,000 websites, Internet users, and organizations plan massive online protest for July 12th. Other participants include Twitter, Amazon, Facebook. Google,  Reddit, Netflix, OK Cupid, Mozilla, Etsy, Kickstarter, Vimeo, and PornHub&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Airbnb, Spotify, Yelp, Snapchat, and Dropbox are the latest major players to announce their participation in the Internet-Wide &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/july12&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Day of Action&lt;/a&gt; to Save Net Neutrality scheduled for July 12th to oppose the FCC’s plan to slash Title II, the legal foundation for net neutrality rules that protect online free speech and innovation. Twitter, Reddit, Netflix, Amazon, Facebook, Google, Kickstarter, Etsy, Vimeo, Private Internet Access, Mozilla, OK Cupid, Imgur, PornHub, Medium, and hundreds of other major sites are also participating. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See the announcement for the day of action here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=https%3A%2F%2Fbattleforthenet.com%2Fjuly12&amp;amp;t=ZjMzZjU3NWNjZThlZWQzNDVmZGU5MTU4NTI4NWIyZmEwZGFiMmI0ZSxBdTdLV0dLRA%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F162821217028%2Flargest-websites-on-earth-prepare-for-net&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://battleforthenet.com/july12&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See examples of what sites are doing on July 12 here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.battleforthenet.com%2Fjuly12%23join&amp;amp;t=MWE1YjE4MzgzNDAyODgzNzU4OGQwYWZkZTkzYTgyYzFjNmM4MTZlNyxBdTdLV0dLRA%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F162821217028%2Flargest-websites-on-earth-prepare-for-net&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.battleforthenet.com/july12#join&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Embed a video about the day of action here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DcIFBb3e3tFA%26feature%3Dyoutu.be&amp;amp;t=MGY2YThjMzU5MTMyMWQzMzEwNmVkYzk4ZmUyODViZTBmMDA1NzgxZixBdTdLV0dLRA%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F162821217028%2Flargest-websites-on-earth-prepare-for-net&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cIFBb3e3tFA&amp;amp;feature=youtu.be&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See graphics usable by press here: &lt;a href=&quot;http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=https%3A%2F%2Fdrive.google.com%2Fdrive%2Ffolders%2F0B7iKho2OIeVzREZWSkRaenZwMFk&amp;amp;t=YzA5ZGE2ZGU5Y2IyNTRmOGE0NDhlYzViNTlhNDM3MTgzNmM1MzUwMixBdTdLV0dLRA%3D%3D&amp;amp;b=t%3AKMlLl9GOPd0Y9ROFg2ygww&amp;amp;p=http%3A%2F%2Ftumblr.fightforthefuture.org%2Fpost%2F162821217028%2Flargest-websites-on-earth-prepare-for-net&amp;amp;m=1&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/0B7iKho2OIeVzREZWSkRaenZwMFk&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The FCC needs to listen to the voices of real people who will be affected by this attack on net neutrality protections &amp;ndash; not just lobbyists from telecom companies in pursuit of more power. The goal of the protest tomorrow is to ensure that ordinary people have a voice and are heard by decision makers in Washington, DC.  No one &amp;ndash; regardless of their political affiliation &amp;ndash; wants their cable company to control what they can see and do on the Internet, or to charge extra fees to access the content they want,” &lt;strong&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, one of the leading organizations behind the protest,&lt;/strong&gt; “The Internet has given more people a voice than ever before, and that transformative power is worth fighting for. July 12th we will come together to defend the future of free speech.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Media attention for online mobilizations tends to focus on the big names participating, but there is a much more interesting story: a rag tag coalition of Internet activists huddled over their laptops in coworking spaces, home offices, and coffee shops, who are the ones who came up with the idea, called for, and organized the protest, and have since been working together to lay the groundwork, build the technical tools, and create the educational resources that make it possible for large and small websites to participate in these mass days of action. It’s a grassroots effort involving dozens of volunteers working together in Slack channels, outreach spreadsheets, endless email chains, organizing in online communities and forums, and an enormous amount of creativity and digital elbow grease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 80,000 people, sites, and organizations have signed on to the effort overall, and more announcements from major companies are expected in the coming days. Participants will display prominent messages on their homepages on July 12 or encourage users to take action in other ways, using push notifications, videos, social media, and emails. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effort is led by many of the grassroots groups behind the largest online protests in history including the SOPA blackout and the Internet Slowdown. The day of action will focus on grassroots mobilization, with public interest groups activating their members and major web platforms providing their visitors with tools to contact Congress and the FCC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other sites and apps participating include Automattic (Wordpress), Soundcloud, Medium, Y Combinator, GitHub, Pantheon, Bittorrent Inc., Shapeways, Nextdoor, Stack Overflow, Funny Or Die, Dreamhost, and CREDO Mobile, Goldenfrog, Fark, Chess.com, Namecheap, DuckDuckGo, Checkout.com, Sonic, Ting, ProtonMail, O’Reilly Media, SlashDot, Dribble, Change.org, Dischord, SourceForge, and Union Square Ventures. Organizations participating include Fight for the Future, Free Press Action Fund, Demand Progress, Center for Media Justice, EFF,  Internet Association, Internet Archive, World Wide Web Foundation, Creative Commons, National Hispanic Media Coalition, Greenpeace, Common Cause, ACLU, Rock the Vote, American Library Association, Daily Kos, OpenMedia, The Nation, PCCC, MoveOn, OFA, Public Knowledge, OTI, Color of Change, MoveOn, Free Software Foundation, Internet Creators Guild, the Women’s March, and many others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2017 08:00:01 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-10-largest-websites-on-earth-prepare-for-net/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-10-largest-websites-on-earth-prepare-for-net/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Largest websites on earth prepare for net neutrality day of action on July 12: Spotify, Facebook, Google, latest to join</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;1479&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;753&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/62a07a02a1885ffb3d6fff545a55fd89/tumblr_inline_osq8ysNCDa1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1479&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;753&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 7, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Thousands of websites plan massive online protest for July 12th. Other participants include Twitter, Amazon, Reddit, Netflix, OK Cupid, Mozilla, Etsy, Kickstarter, Vimeo, and PornHub&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Spotify and ThinkGeek are the latest major players to announce their participation in the Internet-Wide&lt;b&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/july12&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Day of Action&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;to Save Net Neutrality scheduled for July 12th to oppose the FCC’s plan to slash Title II, the legal foundation for net neutrality rules that protect online free speech and innovation. Twitter, Reddit, Netflix, Amazon, Kickstarter, Etsy, Vimeo, Private Internet Access, Mozilla, OK Cupid, Imgur, PornHub, Medium, and hundreds of other major sites are also participating. Yesterday, representatives for Facebook and Google &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.inverse.com/article/33835-google-joins-net-neutrality-day-of-a&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;told&lt;/a&gt; multiple &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mercurynews.com/2017/07/06/tech-companies-to-join-day-of-action-protest-to-protect-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;reporters&lt;/a&gt; that the web giants plan to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We have not heard directly from either Facebook or Google, but we’re glad to hear that these companies are listening to their employees and Internet users and will speak out for net neutrality with the rest of the Internet on July 12,”&lt;b&gt; said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future,&lt;/b&gt; “In previous years these companies have often been on the sidelines of these fights, so we hope that they plan to do something meaningful in the spirit of the protest and educate their users about what’s at stake if we lose net neutrality protections that protect our online free speech, and give them opportunities to take action.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Media attention for online mobilizations tends to focus on the big names participating, but there is a much more interesting story: a rag tag coalition of Internet activists huddled over their laptops in coworking spaces, home offices, and coffee shops, who are the ones who came up with the idea, called for, and organized the protest, and have since been working together to lay the groundwork, build the technical tools, and create the educational resources that make it possible for large and small websites to participate in these mass days of action. It’s a grassroots effort involving dozens of volunteers working together in Slack channels, outreach spreadsheets, endless email chains, organizing in online communities and forums, and an enormous amount of creativity and digital elbow grease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 50,000 people, sites, and organizations have signed on to the effort overall, and more announcements from major companies are expected in the coming days. Participants will display prominent messages on their homepages on July 12 or encourage users to take action in other ways, using push notifications, videos, social media, and emails. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See the announcement for the day of action here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://battleforthenet.com/july12&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://battleforthenet.com/july12&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See examples of what sites are doing on July 12 here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/july12#join&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.battleforthenet.com/july12#join&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effort is led by many of the grassroots groups behind the largest online protests in history including the SOPA blackout and the Internet Slowdown. The day of action will focus on grassroots mobilization, with public interest groups activating their members and major web platforms providing their visitors with tools to contact Congress and the FCC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other sites and apps participating include Soundcloud, Medium, Y Combinator, GitHub, Pantheon, Bittorrent Inc., Shapeways, Nextdoor, Stack Overflow, Funny Or Die, Dreamhost, and CREDO Mobile, Goldenfrog, Fark, Chess.com, Namecheap, DuckDuckGo, Checkout.com, Sonic, Ting, ProtonMail, O’Reilly Media, SlashDot, Dribble, Dischord, SourceForge, and Union Square Ventures. Organizations participating include Fight for the Future, Free Press Action Fund, Demand Progress, Center for Media Justice, EFF,  Internet Association, Internet Archive, World Wide Web Foundation, Creative Commons, National Hispanic Media Coalition, Greenpeace, Common Cause, ACLU, Rock the Vote, American Library Association, Daily Kos, OpenMedia, The Nation, PCCC, MoveOn, OFA, Public Knowledge, OTI, Color of Change, MoveOn, Free Software Foundation, Internet Creators Guild, the Women’s March, and many others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 11:42:02 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-07-largest-websites-on-earth-prepare-for-net/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-07-largest-websites-on-earth-prepare-for-net/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Reports: Facebook and Google say they are joining net neutrality day of action on July 12</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/0c723072ed36022d5a4362103ff1b92a/tumblr_inline_osoy1yFsXf1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;1024&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1024&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 6, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Thousands of websites plan massive online protest for July 12th. Other participants include Twitter, Amazon, Reddit, Netflix, OK Cupid, Mozilla, Etsy, Kickstarter, Vimeo, and PornHub&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Representatives for Facebook and Google &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.inverse.com/article/33835-google-joins-net-neutrality-day-of-a&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;have told&lt;/a&gt; multiple &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mercurynews.com/2017/07/06/tech-companies-to-join-day-of-action-protest-to-protect-net-neutrality/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;reporters&lt;/a&gt; that the web giants plan to participate in the Internet-Wide &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/july12&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Day of Action&lt;/a&gt; to Save Net Neutrality scheduled for July 12th to oppose the FCC’s plan to slash Title II, the legal foundation for net neutrality rules that protect online free speech and innovation. Twitter, Reddit, Netflix, Amazon, Kickstarter, Etsy, Vimeo, Private Internet Access, Mozilla, OK Cupid, Imgur, PornHub, Medium, and hundreds of other major sites are also participating.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We have not heard directly from either Facebook or Google, but we’re glad to hear that these companies are listening to their employees and Internet users and will speak out for net neutrality with the rest of the Internet on July 12,” &lt;b&gt;said Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, &lt;/b&gt;“In previous years these companies have often been on the sidelines of these fights, so we hope that they plan to do something meaningful in the spirit of the protest and educate their users about what’s at stake if we lose net neutrality protections that protect our online free speech, and give them opportunities to take action.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Media attention for online mobilizations tends to focus on the big names participating, but there is a much more interesting story: a rag tag coalition of Internet activists huddled over their laptops in coworking spaces, home offices, and coffee shops, who are the ones who came up with the idea, called for, and organized the protest, and have since been working together to lay the groundwork, build the technical tools, and create the educational resources that make it possible for large and small websites to participate in these mass days of action. It’s a grassroots effort involving dozens of volunteers working together in Slack channels, outreach spreadsheets, endless email chains, organizing in online communities and forums, and an enormous amount of creativity and digital elbow grease. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 50,000 people, sites, and organizations have signed on to the effort overall, and more announcements from major companies are expected in the coming days. Participants will display prominent messages on their homepages on July 12 or encourage users to take action in other ways, using push notifications, videos, social media, and emails. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See the announcement for the day of action here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://battleforthenet.com/july12&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://battleforthenet.com/july12&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See examples of what sites are doing on July 12 here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/july12#join&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.battleforthenet.com/july12#join&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effort is led by many of the grassroots groups behind the largest online protests in history including the SOPA blackout and the Internet Slowdown. The day of action will focus on grassroots mobilization, with public interest groups activating their members and major web platforms providing their visitors with tools to contact Congress and the FCC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other sites and apps participating include Soundcloud, Medium, Y Combinator, GitHub, Pantheon, Bittorrent Inc., Shapeways, Nextdoor, Stack Overflow, Funny Or Die, Dreamhost, and CREDO Mobile, Goldenfrog, Fark, Chess.com, Namecheap, DuckDuckGo, Checkout.com, Sonic, Ting, ProtonMail, O’Reilly Media, SlashDot, Dribble, Dischord, SourceForge, and Union Square Ventures. Organizations participating include Fight for the Future, Free Press Action Fund, Demand Progress, Center for Media Justice, EFF,  Internet Association, Internet Archive, World Wide Web Foundation, Creative Commons, National Hispanic Media Coalition, Greenpeace, Common Cause, ACLU, Rock the Vote, American Library Association, Daily Kos, OpenMedia, The Nation, PCCC, MoveOn, OFA, Public Knowledge, OTI, Color of Change, MoveOn, Free Software Foundation, Internet Creators Guild, the Women’s March, and many others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 18:49:26 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-06-reports-facebook-and-google-say-they-are-joining/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-06-reports-facebook-and-google-say-they-are-joining/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>100+ high-profile online creators sign open letter to FCC and Congress opposing plans to gut net neutrality</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure data-orig-width=&quot;867&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;458&quot; class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/10b11a536fa619b18cfa0eff2fcb3514/tumblr_inline_osnah6tQtR1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; alt=&quot;image&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;867&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;458&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 6, 2017&lt;b&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact: Laura Chernikoff, +1-303-819-8733, laura@internetcreatorsguild.com&lt;br/&gt;Evan Greer, Fight for the Future, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Prominent YouTube creators with over 165 million collective subscribers describe how slashing Title II protections threatens the Internet economy, innovation, and creativity&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;July 6, 2017 – A group of 130 prominent online video creators from across the country have expressed serious concerns with the Federal Communications Commission’s (FCC) plans to roll back net neutrality protections for Internet users across the country. In an &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://internetcreatorsguild.com/net-neutrality&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;open letter&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;released today, creators warn that if the FCC slashes Title II – the strong legal foundation for U.S. net neutrality protections – the impacts of allowing Internet service providers to block, throttle, and charge fees would be immense for online video creators, many of whose audiences rival traditional media in size. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The letter, organized by the &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://internetcreatorsguild.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Creators Guild&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/b&gt; highlights the skyrocketing popularity in video traffic over the past decade, and warns that any weakening of the FCC’s 2015 Open Internet Order “&amp;hellip;would have an outsized impact on our field and jeopardize our livelihood.” The letter&amp;rsquo;s signatories, who collectively reach over 165 million people in their audiences, worry that a loss of net neutrality will give Internet service providers (ISPs) new influence over how online creators are able to grow their businesses. They argue that these protections are crucial to maintaining a level playing field. The organizers are encouraging more people to &lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.google.com/a/fightforthefuture.org/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSfv_XFI8M_OCm7iiL70CpaGqNqDVC1FPU0JoMdA0SW43kRaEA/viewform&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sign on&lt;/a&gt;, as names are being added on rolling basis. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notable signatories include:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;1. Hank and John Green of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/vlogbrothers&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Vlogbrothers&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/scishow&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;SciShow&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/crashcourse&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;CrashCourse&lt;/a&gt; (13 million subscribers)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;2. Benny Fine of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/TheFineBros&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;FineBrothersEntertainment&lt;/a&gt; (15 million subscribers)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;3. Dane Boedigheimer of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/realannoyingorange&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Annoying Orange&lt;/a&gt; (15 million subscribers)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;4. Ned Fulmer of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/BuzzFeedVideo&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BuzzFeedVideo&lt;/a&gt; (12.6 million subscribers)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;5. Burnie Burns of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/RoosterTeeth&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Rooster Teeth&lt;/a&gt; (9 million subscribers)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;6. Meg DeAngelis of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/maybabytumbler&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;MayBaby&lt;/a&gt; (5.6 million subscribers)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;7. Mindy McKnight of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/CuteGirlsHairstyles&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;CuteGirlHairstyles&lt;/a&gt; (5 million subscribers).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;8. Sam Gorski of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/CorridorDigital&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Corridor Digital&lt;/a&gt; (4.3 million subscribers)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;9. Jon Cozart of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/Paint&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Paint&lt;/a&gt; (4 million subscribers)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;10. Kandee Johnson of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/kandeejohnson&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Kandee Johnson&lt;/a&gt; (3.8 million subscribers)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;11. Henry Reich of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/minutephysics&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;MinutePhysics&lt;/a&gt; (3.8 million subscribers)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;12. Rob Czar and Corinne Leigh of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/ThreadBanger&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Threadbanger&lt;/a&gt; (3.7 million subscribers)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;13. Andrew Rose Gregory of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/schmoyoho&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Gregory Brothers&lt;/a&gt; (3 million subscribers)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;14. Julia Gilman of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/BeautyTakenIn&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BeautyTakeIn&lt;/a&gt; (2.6 million subscribers)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;15. Anna Akana of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/user/AnnaAkana&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Anna Akana&lt;/a&gt; (1.8 million subscribers)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Strong, enforceable net neutrality protections are essential to ensure leading figures in online video can continue revolutionizing media and to give opportunities for new voices to gain momentum,” s&lt;b&gt;aid Laura Chernikoff, Executive Director of the Internet Creators Guild.&lt;/b&gt; “Otherwise, deep-pocketed media giants who can afford privileged, fast lane access to customers would empowered to drown out the dynamic and growing industry of internet creators.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The letter also highlights support for net neutrality policies from an overwhelming majority of &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.consumerreports.org/net-neutrality/majority-of-americans-endorse-net-neutrality-protections/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Americans&lt;/a&gt;,&lt;/b&gt; and comes just days in advance of a July 12th Internet-Wide &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/july12&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Day of Action&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt; to Save Net Neutrality. Over 50,000 people and thousands of websites have already joined the online protest, including web giants such as Amazon, Reddit, Netflix, OkCupid, Mozilla, Etsy, Kickstarter, Vimeo, and many others. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The signatories plan to leverage their online reach to encourage their audiences and the American to speak out for strong net neutrality protections. The letter states, “We’re in this for the long-haul. We will fight for as long as it takes to convince you and your colleagues to oppose any legislation or regulatory changes that would threaten real, enforceable Title II net neutrality.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Laura Chernikoff, Executive Director of the Internet Creators Guild, said:&lt;/b&gt; “Online creators and the American public have made their position loud and clear: we need real, enforceable net neutrality rules rooted in Title II of the Communications Act. This is the only way to ensure each of us can continue to live in a country where Internet users have an equal shot at reaching people and earning a living on the open web.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Hank Green, Internet Creators Guild Advisor and creator of Vlogbrothers, SciShow, and CrashCourse said, &lt;/b&gt;“So many individuals and corporations have been given such tremendous economic opportunities thanks to a neutral internet. I am one of them, and it hurts to think the opportunities I&amp;rsquo;ve had might be denied to other people.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This action is part of the &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://internetcreatorsguild.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet Creators Guild’s&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;efforts to advocate for and support creators. The non-profit organization was created in order to bring internet creators together to make their profession more sustainable. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CONTACT INFORMATION:&lt;br/&gt;Laura Chernikoff&lt;br/&gt;Executive Director, Internet Creators Guild&lt;br/&gt;+1-303-819-873&lt;br/&gt;laura@internetcreatorsguild.com&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 21:25:16 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-06-100-high-profile-online-creators-sign-open-letter/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-06-100-high-profile-online-creators-sign-open-letter/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Net Neutrality Day of Action July 12 May Be the Largest Online Protest in Years: Wordpress, Bandcamp among latest to join</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;753&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1479&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/62a07a02a1885ffb3d6fff545a55fd89/tumblr_inline_osmpb5asrN1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;753&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1479&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, July 5, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Thousands of websites plan massive online protest for July 12th. Other participants include Amazon, Reddit, Netflix, OK Cupid, Mozilla, Etsy, Kickstarter, Vimeo, and PornHub&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Urban Dictionary, Bandcamp, Automattic (who run WordPress) and Discord are among latest major web platforms to join the Internet-Wide &lt;a href=&quot;http://battleforthenet.com/july12&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Day of Action&lt;/a&gt; to Save Net Neutrality scheduled for July 12th to oppose the FCC’s plan to slash Title II, the legal foundation for net neutrality rules that protect online free speech and innovation. Twitter, Reddit, Netflix, Amazon, Kickstarter, Etsy, Vimeo, Private Internet Access, Mozilla, OK Cupid, Imgur, PornHub, Medium, and dozens of other major sites are also participating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than 50,000 people, sites, and organizations have signed on to the effort overall, and more announcements from major companies are expected in the coming days. Participants will display prominent messages on their homepages on July 12 or encourage users to take action in other ways, using push notifications, videos, social media, and emails.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See the announcement for the day of action here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://battleforthenet.com/july12&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://battleforthenet.com/july12&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;See examples of what sites are doing on July 12 here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.battleforthenet.com/july12#join&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.battleforthenet.com/july12#join&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effort is led by many of the grassroots groups behind the largest online protests in history including the SOPA blackout and the Internet Slowdown. The day of action will focus on grassroots mobilization, with public interest groups activating their members and major web platforms providing their visitors with tools to contact Congress and the FCC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other sites and apps participating include Soundcloud, Medium, Y Combinator, GitHub, Pantheon, Bittorrent Inc., Shapeways, Nextdoor, Stack Overflow, Funny Or Die, Dreamhost, and CREDO Mobile, Goldenfrog, Fark, Chess.com, Namecheap, DuckDuckGo, Checkout.com, Sonic, Ting, ProtonMail, O’Reilly Media, SlashDot, Dribble, Dischord, SourceForge, and Union Square Ventures. Organizations participating include Fight for the Future, Free Press Action Fund, Demand Progress, Center for Media Justice, EFF,  Internet Association, Internet Archive, World Wide Web Foundation, Creative Commons, National Hispanic Media Coalition, Greenpeace, Common Cause, ACLU, Rock the Vote, American Library Association, Daily Kos, OpenMedia, The Nation, PCCC, MoveOn, OFA, Public Knowledge, OTI, Color of Change, MoveOn, Free Software Foundation, Internet Creators Guild, the Women’s March, and many others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Evan Greer, campaign director of Fight for the Future, said:&lt;/b&gt; “The Internet has given more people a voice than ever before, and we’re not going to let the FCC take that power away from us. Massive online mobilization got us the strong net neutrality protections that we have now, and we intend to fight tooth and nail to defend them. Politicians in Washington, DC need to learn that net neutrality is not a partisan issue and Internet users will not tolerate these attacks on our basic rights &amp;ndash; we will come together to protect the web as an open platform for free expression and exchange of ideas.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Michal Rosenn, General Counsel at Kickstarter, said:&lt;/b&gt; “A threat to net neutrality is a threat to the free exchange of ideas that creative culture and an informed public rely upon. Kickstarter, and the tens of thousands of creators who have brought new ideas to life through our platform, all depend on a free and open internet. We&amp;rsquo;re proud to stand alongside so many others today to preserve net neutrality, and to protect the freedoms that make the internet such a powerful force.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Malkia Cyril, executive director at the Center for Media Justice, said: &lt;/b&gt;&amp;ldquo;Communities of color across the United States depend on an open Internet to thrive. From resisting police violence to demanding fair wages &amp;ndash; the political voice and economic opportunity that the Internet enables must remain protected by Title II net neutrality. Trump&amp;rsquo;s FCC seeks to wall these communities off from the power of the internet as a mobilizing tool and an equalizer. On July 12, we will stand together with activists, Internet users of color, advocacy groups, and tech companies to preserve democracy by defending our Internet.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Michael Cheah, General Counsel, Vimeo, said:&lt;/b&gt; “Net neutrality made it possible for Vimeo, along with countless other startups, to innovate and thrive. The FCC’s proposed rollback of the 2015 open Internet rules threatens to impede that innovation and allow a handful of incumbent ISPs to determine winners and losers. On July 11th, Vimeo will proudly join our fellow tech brethren to rally Internet users nationwide to demand strong net neutrality rules to prevent ISPs from manipulating Internet traffic.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mark Stanley, communications director of Demand Progress, said: &lt;/b&gt;“The FCC&amp;rsquo;s plan to dismantle net neutrality will unfairly pad the bottom lines of Comcast and the rest of Big Cable, while undermining the public’s ability to freely communicate, organize, and innovate. Every few years, a threat so severe confronts the open internet that people, organizations, and companies from across the political spectrum—including some of the largest online platforms—must band together in common cause to fight back. The FCC’s ongoing effort to roll back net neutrality protections represents just such a threat — and on the July 12th day of action, we’ll once again use the transformative power of the internet to defend the internet itself.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Sam Altman, President of Y Combinator, said: &lt;/b&gt;&amp;quot;At Y Combinator, the startup accelerator I run, we have proudly supported thousands of entrepreneurs and more than 1,400 businesses, including companies like AirBnB and Dropbox. Companies like these have gone on to change our lives for the better—how we work, how we eat, how we live. They could grow and compete, and ultimately consumers choose who wins and loses online. Without strong net neutrality rules, though, I’m concerned that the cable and wireless companies that control internet access will have outsized power to pick winners and losers in the market.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Free Press Campaign Director Candace Clement said: &lt;/b&gt;“It’s like déjà vu. The last time Net Neutrality came before the FCC, internet users across the political spectrum swamped the agency with comments demanding strong Net Neutrality protections. The internet won’t go down quietly in 2017 and on July 12 people, companies, organizations and websites will let everyone know that the Trump FCC lacks a public mandate to take away our online rights. We will make it impossible for Chairman Pai to continue to cling to the sorts of alternative facts against Net Neutrality that we’ve proven to be wrong time and again.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Denelle Dixon, Mozilla&amp;rsquo;s Chief Legal and Business Officer, said: &lt;/b&gt;&amp;ldquo;Net neutrality is vital to a healthy Internet: it protects free speech, competition and innovation online. It&amp;rsquo;s also something a majority of Americans support — 76%, according to a recent Mozilla-Ipsos poll. By reverting to a Title I classification for ISPs, the FCC is endangering Americans&amp;rsquo; access to a free and open web. The FCC is creating an Internet that benefits ISPs, not users.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Zachary Rosen, CEO of Pantheon, said:&lt;/b&gt; &amp;ldquo;We started Pantheon to make it easier for organizations big and small to succeed on the Web. But if strong net neutrality rules under Title II go away, it&amp;rsquo;d put both us and our customers&amp;rsquo; innovation at risk.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 13:46:26 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-05-net-neutrality-day-of-action-july-12-may-be-the/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-07-05-net-neutrality-day-of-action-july-12-may-be-the/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Fraudulent comments that undermine the FCC’s net neutrality comment process must be investigated</title>
        
        
          <description>&lt;figure class=&quot;tmblr-full&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;600&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1500&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://68.media.tumblr.com/addd2c2188d5cf5f298c1c6296a1407e/tumblr_inline_os9plmbKdB1ri3xd7_540.png&quot; data-orig-height=&quot;600&quot; data-orig-width=&quot;1500&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR IMMEDIATE RELEASE, June 28, 2017&lt;br/&gt;Contact: Evan Greer, 978-852-6457, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:press@fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;press@fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for the Future praises letter from ranking member of House Energy &amp;amp; Commerce Oversight Committee calling for investigation into hundreds of thousands of fake anti-net neutrality comments&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ranking member of the House Energy and Commerce Oversight Committee Frank Pallone Jr (D-NJ) &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://democrats-energycommerce.house.gov/sites/democrats.energycommerce.house.gov/files/DOJ.FBI_.%202017.06.28.%20Letter%20re%20federal%20law%20violations%2C%20stolen%20identities%2C%20and%20FCC%20open%20comments.%20CAT.%20OI.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;sent a letter&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;to the FBI and Department of Justice this morning calling for law enforcement agencies to investigate the flood of fraudulent anti-net neutrality comments that have been submitted into the FCC’s docket using real people’s names and addresses without their permission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future, a leading digital rights group that has been helping Internet users investigate the fake comments through their &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-05-23-comcast-tries-to-censor-pro-net-neutrality-website/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Comcastroturf.com campaign&lt;/a&gt;, and who helped facilitate &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-05-25-victims-whose-stolen-names-and-addresses-were-used/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;a letter to the FCC&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;from dozens of individuals whose had their personal information used to submit comments without their consent, issued the following statement, which can be attributed to campaign director, Evan Greer (pronouns: she/her):&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;“The FCC under Ajit Pai’s leadership has repeatedly refused to meaningfully address the very serious issue of fake anti-net neutrality comments submitted into its docket using stolen names and addresses. It’s only right that lawmakers are now stepping in and calling for an investigation. &lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Regardless of their views on the FCC’s proceeding, every member of Congress should be concerned if their constituents’ identities are being stolen and used to submit comments to a Federal Agency without their permission, in ways that violate federal law and the privacy rights of the individuals affected.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;The public needs to know who has been attempting to distort the record with these fraudulent comments, whether they were funded by the telecom companies that stand to benefit from the FCC’s attack on net neutrality protections, and whether leadership at the FCC knew about the operation and willfully decided to allow it to continue.&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Federal Agencies have a responsibility to employ basic cybersecurity practices and act transparently to ensure that public comment proceedings have integrity and allow for meaningful input from the public. At this point, the FCC has clearly failed to maintain that integrity in this latest net neutrality proceeding. Members of Congress should work across the aisle to ensure that the agency addresses these serious cybersecurity issues before moving forward with an unpopular plan to dismantle consumer protections”&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fight for the Future is also one of the main organizations behind the massive July 12 Internet-Wide Day of Action for Net Neutrality, &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-06-22-net-neutrality-day-of-action-gets-another-huge/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;which has attracted&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;a wide range of prominent supporters including Amazon, Netflix, Twitter, Kickstarter, Etsy, Mozilla, Reddit, Pornhub, Soundcloud, and Vimeo. The group has been a leading voice calling for transparency and investigations into cybersecurity issues as the FCC for several months, and has compiled &lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-05-18-fcc-ignores-growing-evidence-of-fraud-moves-ahead/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;significant evidence&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/b&gt;of what appears to be a sophisticated astroturfing organization that is attempting to create the false impression of grassroots opposition to net neutrality protections.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;###&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Fight for the Future is a digital rights group best known for organizing some of the largest online protests in history including the SOPA Blackout, Internet Slowdown, Reset the Net, and Rock Against the TPP. Learn more at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.fightforthefuture.org&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://www.fightforthefuture.org&lt;/a&gt; or follow us on Twitter &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/fightfortheftr&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;@fightfortheftr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
        
        <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 13:23:11 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-06-28-fraudulent-comments-that-undermine-the-fccs-net/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.fightforthefuture.org/news/2017-06-28-fraudulent-comments-that-undermine-the-fccs-net/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

